<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<entries>

<text>
A helm worn by Vargram the Bloody Wolf, 
one of the first Tarnished to visit the Roundtable Hold.
Vargram earned his nickname from the white 
wolf pelt that adorns this helm.</text>

<text>
Helm of the enchanted knights that once 
served the Carian royal family.
The enchanted knights, anointed by the Lunar 
Queen, were heroes of the highest honors, 
but fell into disarray with the decline of 
the royal family.</text>

<text>
Headband reserved for the badlands' bravest.
Proof that the wearer has slaughtered countless foes.
Following the example of their chieftain Hoarah Loux, 
the brave warriors of the badlands shun excess adornment.</text>

<text>
Helm of one of sixteen ancient knights who served 
Godfrey, the first Elden Lord.
The axe ornamentation is the knight Ordovis' mark, 
displayed also by his men.
The conduits that cover this armor seethe with the 
power of life's crucible; that which coursed through 
the Erdtree in its primordial form.</text>

<text>
Blindfold of exiled prophets who foresaw that their 
faith would end in flames — and were persecuted and 
driven from their homes as a result.
After all, what use is eyesight to those who claim 
to know the true path?</text>

<text>
A mask of heavy stone resembling the wise Karolos, 
a forefather of the Raya Lucarian resurgence.
Magic scholars wear this mask to show the lineage of 
their glintstone study, as well as their vows of 
virtue and austerity.
An eye for the world and a keen mind — first and 
foremost, a sorcerer must surrender both to their craft.</text>

<text>
Cowl of a nomadic warrior.
The blue color of its fabric symbolizes brisk 
waters, as fluid and flowing as the sword in the 
hand of its wearer.
Just as still waters turn foul, stagnation leads to decay.
The warriors who wear this cowl must remain ever-drifting.</text>

<text>
An oval helmet large enough to cover any head. 
Very heavy and very hard. 
The inside of the helm is pitch black, keeping the 
crazed warrior within from panicking.
Perhaps its rather roomy interior also helps alleviate 
feelings of pressure and claustrophobia.</text>

<text>
Armor worn by Vargram the Bloody Wolf, one of 
the first Tarnished to visit the Roundtable Hold.
According to the old legends, wolves 
are the shadows of the Empyrean.
Vargram aspired to such a state himself.</text>

<text>
Armor of the enchanted knights that once 
served the Carian royal family.
The enchanted knights, anointed by the Lunar 
Queen, were heroes of the highest honors, but fell 
into disarray with the decline of the royal family.</text>

<text>
Pauldron reserved for the badlands' bravest.
Proof that the wearer has slaughtered countless foes.
Following the example of their chieftain Hoarah Loux, 
the brave warriors of the badlands shun excess adornment.</text>

<text>
Armor of one of sixteen ancient knights who 
served Godfrey, the first Elden Lord.
The favored armor of Ordovis of the 
Crucible and his men.
The conduits that cover this armor seethe with 
the power of life's crucible; that which coursed 
through the Erdtree in its primordial form.</text>

<text>
Robe of exiled prophets who foresaw that their 
faith would end in flames — and were persecuted 
and driven from their homes as a result.
Its fabric scrapes against their skin like a file,
and the rickety cart wheel around the neck warns 
passers-by not to lend an ear to their 
meandering sermons.</text>

<text>
Robe worn by Raya Lucaria's magic scholars.
Those who dedicate themselves to the study of glintstones 
formed from starry amber receive this modest 
yet elegant deep blue garb along with their 
vows of virtue and austerity.
But with extended life, one is apt to forget old vows.</text>

<text>
Vest of a nomadic warrior.
The blue color of its fabric symbolizes brisk waters, 
as fluid and flowing as the sword in the hand of its wearer.
Just as still waters turn foul, stagnation leads to decay.
The warriors who wear this cowl must remain ever-drifting.</text>

<text>
Gauntlets worn by Vargram the Bloody Wolf,
one of the first Tarnished to visit the Roundtable Hold.
According to the old legends, wolves 
are the shadows of the Empyrean.
Vargram aspired to such a state himself.</text>

<text>
Gauntlets of the enchanted knights that 
once served the Carian royal family.
The enchanted knights, anointed by the Lunar Queen, 
were heroes of the highest honors, 
but fell into disarray with the decline of 
the royal family.</text>

<text>
Gauntlets reserved for the badlands' bravest.
Proof that the wearer has slaughtered countless foes.
Following the example of their chieftain Hoarah Loux, 
the brave warriors of the badlands shun excess adornment.</text>

<text>
Gauntlets of one of sixteen ancient knights 
who served Godfrey, the first Elden Lord.
The conduits that cover this armor seethe with 
the power of life's crucible; that which coursed 
through the Erdtree in its primordial form.
In time, the strength shown by these knights, 
and even their appearance, came to be looked upon 
with scorn, for having such close resemblance to chaos.</text>

<text>
Manchettes worn by Raya Lucaria's magic scholars.
Made by wrapping a simple cloth around the forearms.</text>

<text>
Gauntlets of nomadic warrior.
Crafted from sturdy leather.</text>

<text>
Greaves worn by Vargram the Bloody Wolf, one 
of the first Tarnished to visit the Roundtable Hold.
According to the old legends, wolves are the 
shadows of the Empyrean. Vargram aspired to 
such a state himself.</text>

<text>
Greaves of the enchanted knights that once 
served the Carian royal family.
The enchanted knights, anointed by the Lunar
Queen, were all decorated heroes, were heroes of 
the highest honors, but fell into disarray with 
the decline of the royal family.</text>

<text>
Gaiters formed only with leather straps.
Common wear in the bandlands.</text>

<text>
Greaves of one of sixteen ancient knights who 
served Godfrey, the first Elden Lord.
The conduits that cover this armor seethe with 
the power of life's crucible; that which coursed 
through the Erdtree in its primordial form.
In time, the strength shown by these knights, and 
even their appearance, came to be looked upon with 
scorn, for having such close resemblance to chaos.</text>

<text>
Trousers of the exiled prophets who foresaw that 
their faith would end in flames — and were 
persecuted and driven from their homes as a result.
Its fabric scrapes against their skin like a file, 
and the rickety cart wheel around the neck warns 
passers-by not to lend an ear to their 
meandering sermons.</text>

<text>
Leggings worn by Raya Lucaria's magic scholars.
Made by wrapping a simple cloth around the legs.</text>

<text>
Greaves of a nomadic warrior.
Crafted from sturdy leather.</text>

</entries>