<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<entries>

<text>
Spirit ashes. Summons the spirits 
of five wandering nobles.
(Summoning consumes FP.)
These ashes contain the spirits of nobles 
who now wander the Lands Between after death.
They seem to have forgotten what they were 
in search of, and now roam aimlessly.</text>

<text>
Spirit ashes.
Summons the spirits of three lone wolves.
(Summoning consumes FP.)
These wolves were chased from their pack, 
and later found company with a human 
outcast — a fellow hunter.
Wolf spirits overwhelm enemies with their 
agility, aiding the summoner in combat.</text>

<text>
Spirit ashes.
Summons the spirit of a noble sorcerer.
(Summoning consumes FP.)
These ashes contain the spirit of a noble 
who studied sorcery at Raya Lucaria.
Wields rudimentary glintstone sorceries; it 
seems that was accomplishment enough for a noble.</text>

<text>
Spirit ashes.
Summons the spirit of a northern mercenary.
(Summoning consumes FP.)
The northern mercenaries are said to carry 
the blood of giants in their veins, 
and wield curved cleavers with ease.
Their bellowing shouts further 
enhance their strength.</text>

<text>
Spirit ashes.
Summons a spirit jellyfish.
(Summoning consumes FP.)
Floating phantom that illuminates its surroundings.
Seemingly the lingering spirit of a young 
girl on an eternal search for her sister, 
with whom she'd promised to see the stars.</text>

<text>
Gravitas A Skill from a great 
white king with stone skin.
Pierce the ground with your armament to damage 
foes as a surge of gravity draws them in.
It can be used on melee armaments 
that are not small.</text>

<text>
Carian Glintsword A Skill used 
by the enchanted Carian Knights.
Your sword becomes a magical glintsword for a 
slash. You can charge this Skill for more power.
It can be used on all types of sword.</text>

<text>
Piercing Fang A Skill used by 
the Bloody Finger hunter Yura.
Starting with your blade held horizontally,
you make a powerful thrust that cannot be blocked.
It can be used on thrusting 
armaments that are not small.</text>

<text>
This Ash of War grants an armament 
the Keen affinity and the following Skill:
Repeating Thrust Twist to build power, 
then unleash a flurry of thrusts.
This Skill takes some time to build up, 
but it is very powerful.
It can be used on all thrusting armaments.
Grants Repeating Thrust Skill
Provides the Keen affinity, which increases 
Dexterity scaling, 
but decreases Strength and Base damage
It can be used on all thrusting weapons.</text>

<text>
Holy Ground Raise your shield to consecrate 
the land to the Erdtree, continuously restoring 
HP and boosting defense for you and 
allies in the area of effect.
It can be used on all types of shield.</text>

<text>
Barricade Shield A Skill made 
famous by Sir Neidhardt.
Focus your energy into your shield,temporarily 
hardening it to deflect greater blows.
It can be used on all types of shield</text>

<text>
A Skill brought to Stormveil 
by knights from lost lands.
Stomp the ground hard to kick 
up a temporary storm.
It can be used on all melee armaments.</text>

<text>
A Skill used by the Stormveil Knights long ago.
Your armament is wrapped in a stormy blade 
that can be fired in rapid succession.
It can be used on all standard slashing armaments.</text>

<text>
A Skill used by dragon-worshippers. 
Your armament calls down a bolt of lightning.
You can fire multiple bolts in rapid succession. 
It can be used on all melee armaments.</text>

<text>
Glintsword Arch A Skill used by 
the enchanted Carian Knights.
Small glintswords form an arch 
and attack automatically.
Attack again for a lunging thrust. 
It can be used on all thrusting armaments.</text>

<text>
This Ash of War grants and armament 
the Quality affinity and the following Skill:
Skill: Determination
A truly knightly Skill. Hold your armament 
to your face and pledge your resolve, 
powering up your next attack.
It can be used on all melee armaments</text>

</entries>