<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<entries>

<text>Leather bag containing a pestle and mortar, small blade, and various other tools.
	Enables item crafting from the main menu.
Provides both means to fight and means to survive.</text>
<text>Map of the western region of Limgrave.
The demense of Limgrave, far south of the Erdtree, is bordered to the northwest by the cliffs of Stormveil, and under its ever-clouded skies roll the great steppes of the pale lands.</text>
<text>A key to a lock inside Stormveil Castle.
Opens a locked door.</text>
<text>Astrology tool used by members of the Carian royal family. Part of a larger instrument, removed and stolen away.

Allows the viewer to better see faraway things.

During the age of the Erdtree, Carian astrology withered on the vine.
The fate once writ in the night skies had been fettered by the Golden Order.</text>
<text>A delicate goldwork ring.
	Can be used as a finger whistle.
	Sound the whistle to summon and ride spectral steed.
	(Dismounts steed when used while on horseback.)
Upon death, the spectral steed can be summoned again, but doing so consumes the Flask of Crimson Tears.</text>
<text>暂缺</text>
<text>Item for online play.
	(Can also be used from the Multiplayer menu.)
	Puts the wearer in ready state to answer should someone in another world call for rescue.
	You will be summoned to their world as a hunter.
When summoned to rescue another player, your objective will be to defeat the invader.</text>
<text>Item for online play.
	(Can also be used from the Multiplayer menu.)
	Allows you to automatically request for a hunter from another world to come to your rescue when your world is invaded.
	(You may be unable to summon rescuers under certain circumstances).
	A lost mystic code, enchanted to take the form of a ring.
One of the fetishes said to have been bestowed by the Two Fingers.</text>
<text>Item for online play.
	(Can also be used from the Multiplayer menu.)
	Craftable item.
	Reveals cooperative and competitive multiplayer signs.
	Cooperative signs will be shown in gold, while competitive signs will be shown in red.
Multiplayer begins when you summon a player from another world through their sign.</text>
<text>Item for online play.
	(Can also be used from the Multiplayer menu.)
	Use as a Host of Fingers to select a summoned player and send them back to their world.
	Use when you have been summoned to another player's world to return to your own world.
This stone blade severs the link formed by a Furled Finger, but the maidens scorn those who revel in overuse.</text>
<text>Item for online play.
	(Can also be used from the Multiplayer menu.)
	Creates a summon sign for cooperative multiplayer.
	Your objective will be to defeat the area boss of the world to which you were summoned.
	A finger of corpse wax, furled like a hook.
It is a relic of those who came before, left to help those who would come after.</text>
<text>Item for online play.
(Can also be used from the Multiplayer menu.)
Creates a summon sign for competitive multiplayer.
Your objective will be to defeat the Host of Fingers of the world to which you were summoned.
A finger of corpse wax, furled like a hook.
The bronze adornments are the mark of a duelist.</text>
<text>Item for online play.
	(Can also be used from the Messages menu.)
	Use to write messages.
	Your messages will be conveyed to other worlds, allowing other players to read them.
	A finger of corpse wax, so emaciated the bone is visible.
	It is a relic of those who came before, left to help those who would come after.</text>
<text>Item for online play.
	(Can also be used from the Multiplayer menu.)
	Attempts an invasion of another player's world.
	If successful, your objective will be to defeat the Host of Fingers of the world to which you were summoned.
	The nail of this finger is shot through with streaks of fresh, glistening blood.
The finger's sickly pale skin feels nothing now, but the nail still aches with sweetest pain.</text>
<text>Item for online play.
	(Can also be used from the Multiplayer menu.)
	Lures in invaders.
	This allows your world to be invaded without any Furled Finger cooperators present, and it also shortens the interval between windows of opportunity for invasion.
	Additionally, enables the arrival of a second invader.
(When two invaders are present, you will be limited to one cooperator.)</text>
<text>A phantom vision of the first grace, which once guided the Tarnished to the Lands Between.
	Lose all runes and return to last site of grace at which you rested.
It all repeats. Be seen by the Elden Ring.Become the Elden Lord.</text>
<text>Online multiplayer item. 
Sends a summon sign for cooperative multiplayer to a nearby summoning pool.
In cooperative multiplayer, you will be summoned to another world to help defeat the area boss.</text>
<text>Item for online play. 
Sends a competitive sign to a nearby summoning pool.
In competitive multiplayer, your objective will be to defeat the Host of Fingers of the world to which you were summoned.</text>
<text>A sacred flask modelled after a golden holy chalice that was once graced by a tear of life.
	Filled with crimson tears, this flask restores HP with use.
	Rest at a site of grace to replenish.
It is said that a Finger Maiden will bestow two such chalices upon the chosen Tarnished when they meet.</text>
<text>A sacred flask modelled after a golden holy chalice that was once graced by a tear of life.
	Filled with cerulean tears, this flask restores FP with use.
	Rest at a site of grace to replenish.
It is said that a Finger Maiden will bestow two such chalices upon the chosen Tarnished when they meet.</text>
<text>Grace that dwells within the inhabitants of The Lands Between; the lingering residue of gold.
	Use to gain runes.
Even now, runes are still imbued with the power of gold. Do you see the Erdtree towering o'er?</text>
<text>Craftable item prepared using a cracked pot.
	Incantations of the Golden Order have been sealed inside.
	Consumes FP.
	Throw at enemy to inflict holy damage.
	Holy water causes significant damage to those who have lived beyond death, and prevents them from rising again.
The Golden Order has no mercy for those who trespass beyond life's bounds.</text>
<text>Ruin fragment inscribed with letters.
Craftable item.
Reveals additional messages from other worlds.
Words are gregarious things, drawn to one another much as people are.</text>
<text>Stone ruin fragment that has undergone some simple processing.
Craftable item.
	Stones such as these shine with the colors of the rainbow, making them useful markers when placed on the ground.
	Can also be dropped to gauge the distance of a fall.
	The more high-pitched the sound it makes, the more likely it is that the fall will be fatal.
Once used to entertain children in the Lands Between.</text>
<text>Preparation of dried rowa fruit.
	Craftable Item.
	Feed to spectral steed while rideng to restore its HP.
Rowa a fruit mildly poisonous and toxic to humans, but Torrent seems to have taste for it.</text>
<text>Craftable item prepared using a cracked pot.
	Incendiary materials have been mixed together and sealed inside, and a short rope that aids throwing has been secured around the pot.
Throw at rearward enemies using the rope, causing the pot to explode and deal fire damage.</text>
<text>Polished stone ruin fragment that shines brighter than a rainbow stone.
	Craftable item.
	Emits light from the location it is placed, illuminating surroundings.
	However, the effect is short-lived, and it lacks the diverse colors of rainbow stones.
May serve some benefit in dark places, or at night.</text>
<text>A relic of the physick chemists, priests of the Erdtree.
Harnesses the powers of crystal tears, which only form after the passage of many moons.
	Various specials effects are bestowed upon the drinker, dependent on the specific mixture of crystal tears.
	Rest at a site of grace to replenish.
It is said that in the Lands Between, pools of crystal tears amass at the bases of Minor Erdtrees.</text>
<text>Grace that dwells within the inhabitants of The Lands 		Between; the lingering residue of gold.
	Use to gain a few runes.
	For all that they may be feeble things, these runes will act as nourishment for the development of any Tarnished.
Provided a Finger Maiden can be found...</text>
<text>Cured strip of meat, dried out after pickling in a green medicinal solution.
	Craftable item.
	Boosts immunity for a short time.
	Immunity governs resistance to various poisons and blights.
The higher it is, the lower the chance of succumbing to such ailments.</text>
<text>Shard of rock found in the wake of a meteorite strike.
It is imbued with a particularly weighty magic.
	Consumes FP.
	Throw at the ground to create a gravitational shockwave.
The desperate ones who scavenge for these shards dub themselves "starcallers".</text>
<text>Turtle neck meat, pickled in a bitter medicinal solution.
	Craftable item.
	Boosts stamina recovery for a short time.
The nutrients churn through the body, practically boiling out heat from the core.</text>
<text>Solidified grease made from a mixture of incendiary materials.
	Craftable item.
	A smallish lump with a short string attached.
	Quickly coats armament, inflicting fire damage.
However, the effects are only brief.</text>
<text>Cured animal liver, dried out after pickling in a flame-hued medical solution.
	Craftable item.
Boosts fire damage negation for a short time, improving damage mitigation against attacks imbued with fire.</text>
<text>Craftable item prepared using a cracked pot.
	 A mixture of incendiary materials has been sealed inside.
Throw at an enemy to cause the pot to explode, inflicting fire damage.</text>
<text>Animal bone sharpened into a knife for throwing.
	Craftable item.
	Throw at enemy to deal damage.
First came into use among the hunters who lay low in the wilds.</text>
<text>Red boluses made from cave moss.
	Craftable item.
	Relieves impending hemorrhage.
	A hemorrhage builds up slowly, causing great damage once the threshold is reached.
Take one of these in timely fashion to avoid such an event.</text>
<text>Four-toed bird foot, pickled in a golden medicinal solution.
Craftable item.
	Boosts the amount of runes obtained from defeating enemies for a short time.
A macabre item, evidence of the desperate ends that those who crave riches will go to.</text>
<text>Boluses made from green cave moss.
	Craftable item.
	Cures poison ailment and relieves poison build-up.
	Poison accumulates gradually, coming into effect once the threshold is reached.
Poison ailment lowers HP in steady increments for a period.</text>
<text>A lump of beast flesh pickled in a medicinal solution mixed with fiery spices.
	Craftable item.
	Boosts physical attack for a short time.
Considered a delicacy in the badlands, this invigorating repast was for the exclusive benefit of those who they called heroes.</text>
<text>Craftable item prepared using a cracked pot.
Filled with the incantations of St. Trina.
Consumes FP.
Throw at enemy to release a purple, soporific haze.
Like a lullaby, or a quagmire, it irresistibly draws its victims down into sleep. Sweet dreams.</text>
<text>Dragon heart seized by a dragon tracker. It has a bizarre shape, mottled by gravel, and it continues to beat vivaciously.
An offering used in the Dragon Communion.
	Consume a dragon's heart at the altar to make its power yours.
While a terrible and savage-looking thing, the heart has a peculiar beauty to it.</text>
<text>Short dagger for throwing.
	It has no handguard.
	The blade is polished, and its weight is expertly balanced.
	Throw at enemy to deal damage.
An auxiliary weapon used primarily to constrain an enemy's movements, it can still be deadly in the right hands.</text>
<text>Stone fragment found near places where ruins have fallen from the sky. 
Can be used for crafting, or simply for throwing at enemies. 
These shards of stone are believed to have once been part of a temple in the sky. 
They glow with a faint light from within.</text>
<text>Stone shard used in a wide range of smithing processes.
	Exceptionally common, it is found throughout the Lands Between
	Used in smithing to strengthen armaments
Smithing stone is distributed widely throughout the terrain of the Lands Between, and mining galleries built to excavate it can be found all over.</text>
<text>Record of crafting techniques left by an armorer who served the great general Radahn.
Contains knowledge of dealing with decay; the application of fire in particular.</text>
<text>Record of crafting techniques left by a man who was denied the path of becoming a Finger Maiden.
He instead became a missionary, spreading holy teachings.(有误)</text>
<text>Record of crafting techniques left by a man who was denied the path of becoming a Finger Maiden.
He instead became a missionary, spreading holy teachings.</text>
<text>A fugitive deserter's record of crafting techniques.
Contains knowledge for surviving in the face of utter scarcity.</text>
<text>Resin secreted from the roots of the Great tree.
	Material used in crafting items.
	The roots of the Great tree drive far and wide through the earth of the Lands Between.

They were once entwined with the roots of the Erdtree, or so they say.</text>
<text>Blood-slick roses that bloom in festering blood.
	Material used for crafting items.
	Particularly beloved by those who serve the Lord of Blood.
Glory to his inevitable reign.</text>
<text>Dark red leaves with thick, swollen veins.
	Material used for crafting items.
	Exceedingly rare to find.
	A faint pulse can be felt in the veins.
Stirs the blood, providing an enlivening effect.</text>
<text>A slice of thinly carved beast flesh.
	Material used for crating items.
	Found by hunting herbivorous beast.
The dried meat toughens the constitution.</text>
<text>The fresh liver of a beast; a luscious fruit of life.
Material used for crating items.
Found by hunting herbivorous beast.
Dried liver boost damage negation.</text>
<text>A lump of beast flesh filled with rich juices.
Material used for crafting items.
Found by hunting carnivorous beast.
 	Meat suitable for a rustic feast.</text>
<text>An eternally burning butterfly found near wildfires and elsewhere.
Material used for crafting items.
Serves as the kindling for a number of items.</text>
<text>Flower that grows in toxic terrain.
	Material used for crafting items.
Poisonous, but may also provide the cure.</text>
<text>Faintly luminescent moss that grows in dark caves.
Material used in crafting items.</text>
<text>Firefly that gives off a silvery light. Material used in crafting items.
	Found near bodies of cold water untouched by sunlight.
	The light of fireflies is believed to have an alluring magic.
Silver light is considered to invite riches.</text>
<text>A splendid, lengthy cut of turtle neck meat.
Material used for crafting items.
Turtle meat is said to boost virility, but none in the Lands Between seem to have much appetite for it these days.
In Lands Between, the urge to reproduce has waned long ago.</text>
<text>Puffy, milky white ovary of a land octopus.
Material used for crafting items.
Land octopuses eat humans in order to bear young, and theirs is the 	blood that runs through these ovaries.</text>
<text>Thin strips of flesh taken from a bloodless creature.
Material used for crafting items.
The dried meat toughens the constitution.</text>
<text>A fungal growth that thrives in damp thickets and elsewhere.
Material used for crafting items.
 Its thick, spongy flesh makes it a key component in throwing pots.</text>
<text>Someone's excrement. It has a golden tinge. Material used for crafting items.
	Often hidden in woods and thickets.
	Gold-tinged excrement is a highly stable substance; it doesn't dry out, nor does it lose its customary warmth or scent.
For better or for worse, it remains as it is.</text>
<text>A large flower that blooms facing the Erdtree.
	Material used for crafting items.
	Exceedingly rare to find.
Though wilted and faded, it still retains holy essence.</text>
<text>Yellow flower that grows in lightning-struck lands.
Material used for crafting items.
Imbued with traces of lightning's essence.</text>
<text>Eggs of great crabs which dwell in the shallows.
	Materials used for crafting items.
	A nutritious foodstuff that warms from within.
The flavor is exquisite.</text>
<text>Head of a large dragonfly.
Material used for crafting items.
Long believed to have the ability to neutralize poisons.</text>
<text>Evergreen leaves that give off a faith light.
	Material used for crafting items.
This very common medicinal plant can be found in thickets and elsewhere.</text>
<text>Owl eggs that will never hatch.
	Material used for crafting items.
Prized as a symbol of the most sublime slumber.</text>
<text>A pale purple water lily that is on the verge of wilting.
	Material used for crafting items.
	Exceedingly rare to find.
	A symbol of faith in St. Trina.
Dulls the senses, preventing agitation.</text>
<text>Berry-like red fruits that grow in shrubs.
	Material used for crafting items.
	Easily found everywhere in the Lands Betwee, it is primarily used in preserved foods.</text>
<text>Thin, hard animal bones.
Material used for crafting items.
Found by hunting beasts.
Commonly used to make disposable weapons</text>
<text>Foot of a four-toed fowl.
	Material used for crafting items.
	In the Lands Between, having three digits is seen as a bad omen.
As such, the rarer four-toed fowl's is a gift of great luck indeed.</text>
<text>Flight feather of a bird of prey.
Material used for crafting items.
Commonly used for arrow fletchings.</text>
<text>Boasting no special qualities, this is merely a goodly length of string. 

Material used for crafting items. 

Often carried by demi-humans. 

Used to make certain items easier to use.</text>
<text>A remnant of bygone research into eternal life. 

This empty pot somehow mends itself when broken. 
Container required for crafting throwing items sealed in pots. 

Sealed within, both materials and mysticism will demonstrate their effects when the pot is thrown.</text>
<text>Unremarkable glintstone, found along roadways everywhere.

Material used for crafting items.

Though too impure to use as a permanent catalyst for glintstone sorcery, it's just about sufficient for crafting disposable sorcerous items.</text>
<text>A dusky-yellow flower that has started to fade and wilt. Material used for crafting items.
	Found throughout the Lands Between.
Said to grow from the old fallen leaves of the Erdtree, these flowers serve as the base material for a number of sorcery techniques.</text>
<text>A special crystallization formed within a tear of life over the course of many moons.
	Causes concoction to explode when taken in mixed physick.
	A dangerous form of crystal tear which possesses absolutely no medicinal qualities.
A lesson said to be learned the hard way for some; faith can be a volatile matter, after all.</text>
<text>A special crystallization formed over the course of many moons within a tear of life, a blessing of the Erdtree.
	Can be mixed in a flask of wondrous physick.
The resulting concoction temporarily raises max stamina.</text>
<text>A special crystallization formed over the course of many moons within a tear of life, a blessing of the Erdtree.
	Can be mixed in a flask of wondrous physick.
The resulting concoction restores half of one's max HP.</text>
<text>A special crystallization formed over the course of many moons within a tear of life, a blessing of the Erdtree.
	Can be mixed in a flask of wondrous physick.
The resulting concoction restores 20% of one's max FP.</text>
<text>Arrow whittled from animal bones.
The tip is set alight before firing.</text>
<text>Arrow whittled from animal bones.
	The tip is set alight before firing.
Deals fire damage to foes.</text>
<text>Arrow whittled from thin animal bones.
Though the arrowhead is sharp indeed, it doesn't fly particularly true.</text>
<text>Arrow whittled from thin animal bones.
The feather fletchings add distance and accuracy to the standard bone arrow.</text>
<text>Arrow whittled from animal bones.
	The tip is daubed with venom.
	Afflicts targets with poison.
Craftable item.</text>
<text>Arrow whittled from animal bones.
	The tip is daubed with venom.Afflicts targets with poison.
	Craftable item.
The addition of fletching enables more precise shots that can travel farther.</text>
<text>Arrow carved to resemble a withered water lily.
	Afflicts targets with a powerful soporific effect.

	Once served an exclusively ritual use by the priests of St. Trina.
The peace of deepest slumber can be so very hard to resist.</text>
<text>Arrow whittled from animal bones.

	The tip is daubed with a water lily tincture.

	Afflicts targets with drowsiness.

	Craftable item.

The addition of fletching enables more precise shots that can travel farther.</text>

</entries>