<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<entries>




<text> 
A glintstone sorcery discovered at the Raya Lucaria Academy.

The glintstone serves as a conduit, launching magical projectiles at foes.
This sorcery can be cast repeatedly and while in motion.

This is a universal first step on the journey to true knowledge of sorcery. </text>

<text> 
 A glintstone sorcery discovered at the Raya Lucaria Academy. 

Fires highly directable magic shooting stars. 
This sorcery can be cast repeatedly and while in motion, and it increases in power when charged up. 

An ancient sorcery, thought to be close to the primeval current itself.</text>

<text> 
A glintstone sorcery discovered at the Raya Lucaria Academy. 

A horizontal arc of magic spreads outward. 

This sorcery can be cast repeatedly and while in motion.

This sorcery is granted to sorcerers who set off from the Academy to travel, in order to protect them against large groups of would-be adversaries. Fools often roam in packs.</text>


<text> 
A lost, ancient glintstone sorcery used by wretches who dwell in underground ruins. 
Produces several bubbles of magic that drift until they naturally pop. 
Charging up this sorcery makes the bubbles linger for a longer time.</text>

<text> 
An aberrant sorcery, discovered along with red glintstone by those exiled to the north for their crimes. 

Summons large thorns from a whorl of blood shed by one's own hand in penance for sins. 

This sorcery can be cast repeatedly.The Academy reviles this sorcery, which draws its power from faith. </text>

<text> 
A glintstone sorcery that draws on gravitational force, used by a great white king with stone skin. 
Calls small meteorites down from the sky. 
The meteor shower continues for as long as the sorcery is in effect. 
It is said that, in the Eternal City, now lost in ruin underground, meteorites held the same import as stars.</text>

<text> 
A glintstone sorcery used by the enchanted knights who served the Carian royal family.
Forms a magic sword to impale one's foes.
This sorcery increases in power when charged up.
Blades of pure moonlight epitomize the protection the moon grants to Caria.</text>

<text> 
An incantation taught by maidens of the Finger Reader.
Heals a small amount of HP.
This incantation can be cast while in motion.
The maidens serve the Two Fingers by guiding the Tarnished to grace, in accordance with its mighty will.</text>


<text> 
An incantation taught by maidens of the Finger Reader.
Heals HP for the caster and nearby allies.
The maidens serve the Two Fingers by guiding the Tarnished to grace, in accordance with its mighty will.</text>


<text> 
An incantation taught by maidens of the Finger Reader.
Cures the poison status ailment and reduces poison gauge build-up.
This incantation can be cast while in motion.
The poison gauge fills steadily.When it is full, you will become poisoned.Your HP will continuously decrease while you are poisoned.</text>

<text> 
An incantation taught by maidens of the Finger Reader.Produces a shockwave that pushes away foes near the caster.
This incantation increases in power when charged up.Hark, Tarnished! If you truly walk in faith, you must be prepared to reject all else! </text>

<text> 
An incantation used by Golden Order fundamentalists.Produces an arc of gold that deals holy damage.
This incantation is especially damaging to those who have lived beyond death.Any felled by this incantation cannot be revived.
These fundamentals hold that, through study guided by the laws of the Golden Order, knowledge itself is the root of holiness. </text>

<text> 
 An incantation from the Fire Monks, guardians of the giants' flame of ruin.
	Momentarily sparks a roaring flame from the caster's hands.
This incantation can be cast rapidly after dashes, dodge rolls, and other maneuvers.</text>

<text> 
An incantation from the Fire Monks, guardians of the giants' flame of ruin.
Produces and throws a ball of raging fire.
Charging up this incantation makes it more powerful and cases the ball to explode.
Fire beguiles those who look upon it.Those who would guard the flame would also come to worship it. </text>

<text> 
An incantation bestowed upon those who cull the Deathroot by Gurranq, the Beast Clergyman.
	Creates beast claws that tear apart the land.This incantation increases in power when charged up.
Long ago, Gurranq was a beast of such terrifying ferocity that his former name meant "Death of the Demigods."</text>

<text> 
An incantation of the Dragon Communion, used by those who've eaten of a dragon's heart.
Spews flaming breath with draconic power.
Those extraordinary individuals who perpetuate the Dragon Communion are called the dragon-hearted. </text>

<text> 
 An incantation of the Dragon Communion, used by those who've eaten of a dragon's heart.
Manifests the power of the Great Ancient Dragon Grayoll to sound a fearsome roar.
The roar of the great Grayoll, foreboding as a mountain, overcomes all who hear it with its might.
Their attack power is temporarily decreased.</text>

<text> 
 An incantation from the maddening Three Fingers.
Causes the yellow flame of frenzy to burst forth from the caster's eyes.
This incantation can drive human foes mad, and charging up makes it more powerful.
Those whose eyes are afflicted with the flame of frenzy are racked with maddening pain and unstoppable tears.</text>




</entries>