<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<entries>

<text> 
Carried by the noble servants of the Lord of Blood.
The vicious design of the dagger allows it to tear 
the wound when stabbing, and the thick coating of 
blood on its blade is the proud mark of its 
effectiveness at inflicting hemorrhaging.
Weapon Skill: Reduvia Blood Blade</text>

<text> 
A thick, solid slab of wood used as a bludgeon.
No skill is required to wield this striking weapon.
A simple, primitive weapon that requires only brute 
strength and persistence to hammer your foe into 
the ground.
Weapon Skill: Brave War Cry</text>

<text> 
A large sword with a straight blade.
This heavy sword is normally wielded with two hands, 
but those with sufficient strength can wield it 
in one alone.
The hefty blade can be swung into multiple foes 
at once thanks to the broad, sweeping attack, making 
fending off crowds all the easier.
Weapon Skill: Step In (Upward Cut)</text>

<text> 
Greatsword of Ordovis, one of the two honored as 
foremost among the knights of the Crucible. 
This sword is imbued with an ancient holiness. 
Its scarlet tint exemplifies the nature of primordial 
gold, said to be close to life itself.
Weapon Skill: Ordovis' Vortex</text>

<text> 
A thick, heavy blade attached to a handle.
The most commonly seen variety of axe.
Axes are known to have been favored by the 
Warrior-King who led the Long March. 
They are also regarded for their 
powerful charge attacks.
Weapon Skill: Frenzy</text>

<text> 
A small bow for firing arrows from a distance.
Can rapidly fire a volley of shots, and is suited 
to use on horseback.</text>

<text> 
A staff with a blue glintstone embedded in the tip.
Serves as a catalyst for glintstone sorcery.
Containing a blue glintstone - the symbol of the 
Carian royal family - this staff makes their glintstone 
sorcery stronger.
Skill: None</text>

<text> 
A spear with winged ornamentation at the base of its head.
A thrusting weapon with long reach that can be used to 
attack from behind a shield.
It is also effective against mounted foes</text>

<text> 
Considered a type of greatspear, this weapon has no blade, 
but instead features a long, conical body designed to pierce.
Though heavy and hard to wield, this weapon displays its 
worth in horseback combat whether mounted or even on foot.</text>

<text> 
A curved sword with a single-sided blade.
Delivers slashing attacks with its sharp blade, but is 
ineffective against armor and hides covered in tough scales.
Smaller in size than most curved swords, it carves into 
enemies with quick, sharp cuts.
Weapon Skill: Spinning Slash</text>

<text> 
A weapon forged from the memories of dragonkin soldiers,
burnished with the essence of draconic immortality.
Alas, the dragonkin never attained immortality, and perish 
as mere imitations of the ancient dragons.
Weapon Skill: Hailstorm Sword</text>

<text> 
A sacred seal given by maidens of the Finger Readers 
which serves as a catalyst for casting sacred incantations.
Incantations must be memorized first at a site of lost 
grace, and a sacred seal must be equipped to cast them
Skill: None</text>

<text> 
A sacred seal given by Gurranq, the Beast Clergyman, which 
serves as a catalyst for casting sacred invocations.
Sacred invocations must be memorized first at a site of lost 
grace, and a sacred seal must be equipped to cast them.
Skill: None</text>

<text> 
A sword with blades on both sides of the hilt.This weapon 
is difficult to wield, and requires high dexterity.
Can be wielded with a single hand, but its true strength 
is enabled with dual-handed spinning attacks.
Weapon Skill: Spinning Slash</text>

<text> 
The Longsword scales primarily with Strength and is a 
good Weapon for melee users who want to remain mobile 
during combat.</text>

<text> 
A small, wooden roundshield. It is light and easy to use, 
but cannot offer the damage negation of a metal shield.
Its emblem is an ancient red thorn design. Though it isn't 
much, it offers greater fire damage negation 
than most shields.
Shield Skill: Parry</text>

<text> 
A creaky old wooden shield, circular in shape.Roughly 
reinforced with vines or some such.
To be blunt, there are far better shields available.
You would do well to leave this one in the garbage 
where it belongs.
Shield Skill: Parry</text>

<text> 
A small iron roundshield.
It is well-balanced and offers impressive damage reduction 
for a small shield.
Shield Skill: Parry</text>

<text> 
A small metal roundshield.The bump in the center enables 
parrying techniques.
A well-timed parry can break an enemy's stance, allowing a 
critical hit.Best suited for those prepared to take the 
risk to reap their reward.
Weapon Skill: Buckler Parry</text>

<text> 
A teardrop-shaped shield embedded with blue glintstones.
Carried by the knights who served the Carian royal family.
This shield demonstrates its true value when confronting 
sorcerers - the Carian Knights were originally established 
to counter the Academy.
Shield Skill: Sorcerer Hunter</text>

<text> 
A round shield covered in leather. 
One of the larger categories of medium-sized shield.
Its damage reduction may be primitive compared to a metal 
shield's, but it can handle a wide range of attack affinities.
Shield Skill: Parry</text>

<text> 
An extremely odd shield adorned with a coiled bronze snake.
An excellent choice for attention——seekers.
This Shield provides an effective defense 
against poison——after all, how does one 
poison a poisonous snake?
Shield Skill: Viper Bite
This shield infused and buffed
Coil Shield Upgrades go here
Other notes and player tips go here</text>

</entries>