<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<entries>

<text> No armament equipped. Bare fists will be used to attack. </text>
<text> A standard dagger with a straight blade. Though modest in reach and capacity for harm, this weapon is light enough to jab in rapid succession and delivers devastating critical hits. </text>
<text> Dagger once belonging to one of the assassins who murdered Godwyn the Golden on the Night of the Black Knives. A ritual performed on the oddly misshapen blade imbued it with the power of the stolen Rune of Death. </text>
<text> A knife with curved handguards. Designed to parry, turning foes' attacks against them. For masters of combat who anticipate every enemy strike and counter accordingly, this weapon is all they need. </text>
<text> Dagger favored by military physicians in white. The pointed blade is hard and sharp, making critical hits especially potent. Medicine is mercy, and mercy upon the battlefield is ruthless. Beware the killers clothed as men of compassion. </text>
<text> Jagged dagger with a distinctive curved blade. Used by the noble servants of the Lord of Blood. This dagger rips the flesh as it enters, inflicting blood loss with sickening efficacy. A proud testament to the success of its vicious design, this weapon is perpetually coated in blood. </text>
<text> A knife made by sharpening hard crystal. Signature weapon of glintstone miners. Used as tool to extract glintstone from broken rock, and as such a faint magic enwreathes the blade. </text>
<text> Sickle decorated with flowers and many-colored fabrics. Ceremonial tool used by dancers during the festivities of Dominula. Its attacks can slip through an enemy's guard. Crafted from human bone. Grants trace amounts of runes on landing attacks. </text>
<text> Ritual blade once presented to Leyndell by the Academy of Raya Lucaria to celebrate their newfound peace. Though the weapon is embedded with precious glintstones and features Erdtree ornamentation, the undulating blade is symbolic of an ancient ritual. </text>
<text> Dagger fashioned from a great scorpion's tail, glistening with scarlet rot. A ceremonial tool used by heretics, crafted from the relic of a sealed outer god. </text>
<text> Large knife with a broad, curved blade. This weapon is designed to slash and rend, inflicting blood loss upon the recipient. </text>
<text> Short sword with a tempering pattern on the blade. A weapon unique to warriors of the Land of Reeds. Afflicts targets with blood loss. These swords are considered auxiliary weapons. Yet, one man is known to wield this weapon in his left hand while using a full-sized katana in his right. A demonic swordsman known only as Okina. </text>
<text> Short sword given to high ranking clergymen of Farum Azula. Raises potency of bestial incantations. The design celebrates a beast's five fingers, symbolic of the intelligence once granted upon their kind. </text>
<text> Sickle fashioned from ivory. Weapon carried by aged Albinaurics. These weapons are evidence of their dedication to the Haligtree, despite never having entered its presence. </text>
<text> Dagger with a bloodstained blade. Afflicts targets with blood loss. As blood darkened the dagger through repeated slashing and stabbing, its blade only grew sharper and harder. </text>
<text> An erdsteel dagger with a grass crest engraved upon its blade. Carried by the Erdtree royalty for self-defense in times of peace. Though forged to a high standard, the weapon is difficult to wield. Attack power also scales with faith. </text>
<text> Dagger given to one who set out on a journey to fulfill her duty long ago. The power of its former owner, the kindling maiden, is still apparent. The one who walks alongside flame, Shall one day meet the road of Destined Death. </text>
<text> A straight sword with a double-edged blade. In addition to its reliable standard damage, this weapon also boasts powerful piercing attacks. A superbly balanced armament. </text>
<text> A short straight sword with a short blade. In addition to its reliable standard damage, this weapon also boasts powerful piercing attacks. Lightweight amongst straight swords, this weapon is easy to wield, requiring only humble attributes. </text>
<text> A straight sword with a wide blade, suited to slashing attacks. Horizontal swings boast wide attack range, making it easier to connect with foes. </text>
<text> Well-crafted straight sword with an illustrious design, wielded by regulars of a lord's army. Though blackened and damaged by years of use, it appears to have otherwise been kept in a serviceable condition, despite the soldiers having long since lost their minds. </text>
<text> Straight sword with a rather short but wide blade. Simple to wield, it was known as the sword of the people. Though the Erdtree styling is still visible, time has not been kind to this sword, now merely a shadow of its former self. </text>
<text> Slender straight sword patterned after an antique ornament. Superior swordsmen prefer to wield one in each hand. After falling from grace, the dregs of the golden lineage sought power and purpose in the past. </text>
<text> A sword made to commemorate the death of Godwyn the Golden, first of the demigods to die. Infused with the humble prayer of a young boy; "O brother, lord brother, please die a true death." </text>
<text> A grim weapon wielded by swordsmen of the Eternal City, this shotel has a blade as fine as a needle. Forged from the liquid metal of a Silver Tear, it is thoroughly tempered until hardened. </text>
<text> Sword forged by compounding silver and gold. A sacred weapon to hunt Those Who Live in Death. Deals holy damage.  The inseparable twins found solace in the Golden Order, the only institution not to revile them as accursed beings. </text>
<text> Hidden sword once granted to the Tarnished of the Roundtable by the Two Fingers. A formless cipher comprises its blade, which deals holy damage no shield can repel. Champions would gather at the Roundtable Hold in days long past, when the Two Fingers were masters of oration, their flesh yet full of vigor. </text>
<text> Storied sword and treasure of Caria Manor. One of the legendary armaments. Astrologers, who preceded the sorcerers, established themselves in mountaintops that nearly touched the sky, and considered the Fire Giants their neighbors. </text>
<text> Sword fashioned from pure crystal; a deed impossible for a human. Enwreathed with powerful magic, its attack scales with intelligence. The inscrutable Crystalians have but one clear purpose; to safeguard their crystals unto the end. One theory posits that they yearn for the return of their creator who will carve for them new brethren. </text>
<text> Straight sword embedded with a blue glintstone. Weapon of knights sworn to Carian royalty. These knights' swords could serve as catalysts, letting them wield sorcerous battle skills. Despite numbering fewer than twenty, this power made them a match for even the champions of gold in battle. </text>
<text> Silver sword carried by clerics of St. Trina. Inflicts sleep ailment upon foes. St. Trina is an enigmatic figure. Some say she is a comely young girl, others are sure he is a boy. The only certainty is that their appearance was as sudden as their disappearance. </text>
<text> Sword forged by servants of Miquella of the Haligtree, with a design modeled after those carried by Carian knights. Instead of glintstone however, amber from the Haligtree is embedded in the blade. A sumptuous piece, yet it has never been offered to any knight—an ill-starred sword with no master. </text>
<text> Beloved sword of an aged knight whose last quest was long behind him, repurposed into a walking stick. The tip is rather worn. Though bent of back and without the brawn required even to raise the sword aloft, still he wished to meet his end with weapon in hand. </text>
<text> Treasured sword of Eochaid, a lesser, long-vanished domain. The copper coloration is not to be confused for rust, but is a conduit for its wielder to move it by their will alone. Swords of Eochaid dance through the skies. </text>
<text> Narrow blade carried by wandering nobles. Made to be easy to wield. Daubed with gold from tip to tail, it should fetch a good sum. </text>
<text> Talon-swords are affixed to the legs of Stormveil's warhawks, but this one has been repurposed for human use. The blade is thin and lightweight so as not to obstruct the hawk's mobility. </text>
<text> A sword with a glintstone in its handguards. Wielded by scholars of the Lazuli Conspectus who seek to master Carian sorcery. Deals magic damage. Apparently once used as a staff of sorcery, this sword is made of wood. </text>
<text> Sword fashioned from pure crystal; a deed impossible for a human. Enwreathed with powerful magic, its attack scales with intelligence. </text>
<text> A large sword with a straight blade. This heavy sword is usually wielded with two hands, but for those with enough strength, one is sufficient. The hefty blade can be swung into multiple foes at once thanks to the broad, sweeping attack, making fending off crowds all the easier. </text>
<text> Oddly shaped greatsword wielded by imps. The gently undulating forked blade is known as an "imp's tongue" and causes blood loss. </text>
<text> Greatsword with a blade of unusually thick steel. A coarse weapon to which polishing is a foreign concept. Weighty even among others of its class, the impact of each strike is sure to be felt. </text>
<text> Well-crafted straight sword with an illustrious design, wielded by regulars of a lord's army. Though blackened and damaged by years of use, it appears to have otherwise been kept in a serviceable condition, despite the soldiers having long since lost their minds. </text>
<text> Greatsword bestowed upon skilled swordsmen in the demigods' service, and yet had no rank or title. Featuring a long grip enabling dual-handed use, this weapon was designed to dispatch larger foes. Being charged with such a duty was undoubtedly a great honor. </text>
<text> Greatsword featuring a flame-like undulation. Shreds enemy flesh, inducing blood loss. Scarlet rot is kept at bay with flame at Redmane Castle, and as such, this beloved sword of Jerren's eventually became the symbol of the castle itself. </text>
<text> Greatsword of Ordovis, one of the two honored as foremost among the Crucible Knights. This sword is imbued with an ancient holy essence. Its red tint exemplifies the nature of primordial gold, said to be close in nature to life itself. </text>
<text> Greatsword forged from a blue-white meteoric ore. The blade conceals gravity-manipulating magic. A weapon unique to the Alabaster Lords, a race of ancients with skin of stone who were said to have risen to life when a meteor struck long ago. </text>
<text> A finely-crafted greatsword intricately engraved with an ancient motif. Given to knights who, whether by misfortune or misdeed, were forced to abandon their homes. Most of these knights were sent to the fringes, where they were forced to start anew with only despair for company. </text>
<text> A Moon Greatsword, bestowed by a Carian queen upon her spouse to honor long-standing tradition. One of the legendary armaments. Ranni's sigil is a full moon, cold and leaden, and this sword is but a beam of its light. </text>
<text> Sword wrought from the remains of a god who should have lived a life eternal. Thoughts on what the weapon portends are many and varied. Some consider it the mark of a great sin, or a sign of great devastation. Some think it as the end of an age, while others; the beginning. </text>
<text> Greatsword patterned after the black steeple of the Helphen, the lampwood which guides the dead of the spirit world. The lamplight is similar to grace in appearance, only it is said that it can only be seen by those who met their death in battle. </text>
<text> Sacred sword of Rykard, Lord of Blasphemy. Remains of the countless heroes he has devoured writhe upon the surface of this blade. Now they share the same blood, bound together as family. Some HP is restored upon defeating an enemy. </text>
<text> Storied sword of House Marais, the family of executioners who presided over the Shaded Castle. One of the legendary armaments. Elemer of the Briar, the Bell Bearing Hunter, snatched the sword from the site of his looming execution, and furnished it with battle skills from his home of Eochaid. </text>
<text> Sinister greatsword fashioned from a giant's backbone. The spines along each side of the blade have been tapered to a fine point and mete out wounds like a lopsided saw-blade. Milos was undersized for a giant, and was viewed as sullied and terribly grotesque. </text>
<text> Greatsword made of light, modeled after the Elden Ring itself. Forged by King Consort Radagon to proudly symbolize the tenets of the Golden Order. One of the legendary armaments. Telltale signs betray that this was once the greatsword bequeathed to him by his first wife, Rennala. </text>
<text> A large sword with a long, straight blade. This heavy sword is usually wielded with two hands, but for those with enough strength, one is sufficient. In addition to the heavy sweeping attacks, it can also make a heavy piercing thrust, making this a versatile weapon. </text>
<text> Bronze greatsword wielded by Valiant Gargoyle. Just like the wielder, the missing parts have been mended with corpse wax; a patchwork of champions. </text>
<text> Barbed rod carried by Deathbirds. The birds are graveyard fire keepers; it is said they rake out the ashen remains of the dead from their kilns. </text>
<text> Bronze greatsword wielded by Valiant Gargoyle, mended with blackened corpse wax. Deals holy damage. Such is the mark of those who serve Maliketh, the Black Blade. </text>
<text> A coarse iron lump of an ultra greatsword. Mows down foes by utilizing its incredible weight. Though handling it likely requires the wielder to have surpassed the realm of the merely human, it is precisely for this reason the weapon is used to slaughter even inhuman foes. </text>
<text> Stone greatsword wielded by Erdtree Burial Watchdogs. Though decorated with the watchman's eye, the pupil was taken by graverobbers and is now hollow, leaving this sword a mere lump of stone. </text>
<text> Maliketh's black blade which once harbored the power of the Rune of Death. A sad shadow of its former glory. After a fragment of Death was stolen on that fateful night, Maliketh bound the blade within his own flesh, such that none might ever rob Death again. </text>
<text> Sword given to the giants who fought for the Erdtree during the War against the Giants long ago. Though the giants have lost their minds, they stay inseparable from their swords that are in sad shape—such that the gold plating had flaked away. </text>
<text> Just about the largest sword a mere man is capable of swinging. True to its name, it is designed to be wielded in both hands, but those of merely ordinary strength will still struggle to do so. The long blade is heavy and sharp, sending foes reeling back with its broader strokes, while also capable of a devastating piercing thrust. </text>
<text> Curved greatswords of black steel wielded by General Radahn. A pair of weapons decorated with a lion mane motif. Radahn earned considerable renown as the Starscourge in his youth, and it is said that it was during this time he engraved the gravity crest upon these blades. </text>
<text> Greatsword decorated in royal Carian style. Favored weapon of Blaidd the Half-Wolf. In defiance of the fate he was born to, Blaidd swore to serve no master but Ranni. As proof, the sword was imbued with a cold magic at the moment the oath was sworn. </text>
<text> Sacred sword of the Dusk-Eyed Queen who controlled the Godskin Apostles before her defeat at the hands of Maliketh. The black flames wielded by the apostles are channeled from this sword. </text>
<text> Originally rubble from a ruin which fell from the sky, this surviving fragment was honed into a weapon. One of the legendary armaments. The ruin it came from crumbled when struck by a meteorite, as such this weapon harbors its destructive power. </text>
<text> The storied sword of Castle Morne. A revenger's weapon, it is burdened with oceans of anger and regret. One of the legendary armaments. A lone surviving champion from a country now vanished was so determined to continue fighting that he claimed the swords of an entire clan of warriors. </text>
<text> Greatsword embedded with a blue glintstone. Weapon of the trolls in service to the royal family of Caria. Called into service when the Queen invoked an oath they swore, the trolls are treated as true knights of Caria, and fight arm in arm with their human comrades. </text>
<text> Large piercing sword with a long, hard bladed edge which is also capable of slashing attacks. For its large size, it can be wielded rather nimbly, leaving little opportunity for the enemy to counter. </text>
<text> Piercing sword of the Cleanrot Knights who fought alongside Malenia, Blade of Miquella. Mainly used as a backup weapon, in combination with a long-handled armament. </text>
<text> A piercing sword with a sharp, slender blade. In addition to this weapon's thrusting attack prowess, it also boasts the ability to be used while guarding with a shield. As one of the smaller piercing swords, quick successive thrusts are easy to perform, but without a cutting edge, it cannot be used for slashing attacks. </text>
<text> Piercing sword of superior quality, featuring intricate ornamentation. Signature weapon of the sorcerer Rogier. High dexterity is required to wield the blade to its full potential, but mastery is a sight to behold, characterized by a flowing style which excels in successive attacks. </text>
<text> Spur of a giant ant which has been fashioned into a rapier. The blade drips with scarlet rot. Scarlet rot is an old legend, of which Maleigh Marais of the Shaded Castle was a private believer. And indeed, he eventually found his own personal goddess. </text>
<text> A razor-thin piercing blade of ice. Forged by Iji, the Carian Royal Blacksmith. Can inflict frost upon enemies, and launch its blade with a strong attack. The blade immediately regenerates. </text>
<text> Estoc carried by wandering nobles. Made to be easy to wield. Daubed with gold from tip to tail, it should fetch a good sum. </text>
<text> Ominous piercing sword with a winding blade. Carried by the noble servants of the Lord of Blood. Designed to bore into flesh, causing severe blood loss at the wound. The extracted blood trickles gracefully down the length of the blade. </text>
<text> Elegant piercing sword with a celadon colored blade wielded by Godskin Nobles. The nobles possess skill with the sword unmatched by any lowborn. Despite its size, successive attacks from this weapon are swifter than the eye can follow. </text>
<text> Large rapier featuring a thin, sharp blade. Commonly used in life or death duels. Like its smaller counterparts, it is made for thrusting attacks, and can be used while guarding with a shield. </text>
<text> Piercing Gravel Stone sword containing primeval lightning. A portion of the Dragonlord's power, gained from a remembrance. This weapon commands great power over the paltry, mortal dragons of today. </text>
<text> A curved sword with a single-sided blade. Delivers slashing attacks with its sharp blade, but is ineffective against thick armor and hides covered in tough scales. Wielders of the weapon employ a unique style that enhances attacks with spinning motions. </text>
<text> Curved sword forged of dull iron wielded by the beastmen of Farum Azula. The blade is heavy but well-balanced. Comparatively easy to wield for the damage it delivers. </text>
<text> Curved sword with a severely hooked blade. Its attacks can slip through an enemy's guard. Made to hunt down humans, this weapon requires high dexterity to wield effectively. </text>
<text> Curved sword with a thin blade of ample length. Light of weight despite its larger size, its slicing attacks come in rapid succession. A devastatingly powerful weapon in the hands of a skilled swordsman. </text>
<text> Curved sword with a light, crescent-shaped blade. Used by the bandits who ran rampant in the wake of the Shattering. Most of the blade is now darkened and covered in rust, but with enough dexterity this weapon may still stand up to some use. </text>
<text> Curved sword with a blade fashioned from the lava of Mt. Gelmir. An armament of the man-serpents, impossible for a human to have made. Deals fire damage. </text>
<text> Legends speak of a master of the sword garbed in blue, and his curved blade that was patterned after flowing water. Strong attack unleashes a series of strikes akin to a dance, offering a glimpse into the legend. </text>
<text> Sword fashioned from a delicate wing, suffused with the magic of the stars. Strong attack unleashes a wave of enchanted light. Crafted from a relic of the Naturalborn of the Void who is said to have assailed the Eternal City. </text>
<text> Unique curved sword, notched like shark's teeth. Weapon carried by corpse pillagers who prowl the sites of old battles. The blade is tacky with blood and covered in hefty nicks, making it totally uneven. Life can be sinister indeed. </text>
<text> Storied sword and treasure of Castle Sol that depicts an eclipsed sun drained of color. One of the legendary armaments. In Sol, the sight of an eclipse inspires a dreadful awe, preventing an onlooker from averting his gaze. </text>
<text> Curved sword fashioned in the image of an ancient serpent deity and tool of a forgotten religion practiced on Mt. Gelmir. Formerly used to offer up sacrifices, this sword restores HP upon slaying an enemy. </text>
<text> A curved sword with a blade at both ends wielded by the Cemetery Shades, the insect-ridden grave keepers. The blade is thin and sharp, and strong attack unleashes a far-reaching slash. </text>
<text> A curved sword with a single-sided blade. Delivers slashing attacks with its sharp blade, but is ineffective against thick armor and hides covered in tough scales. Smaller in size than most curved swords, it carves into enemies with quick, sharp cuts. </text>
<text> Curved sword boasting a large blade. This weapon is designed to make use of its weight in combination with its sharp cutting edge. A thoroughly reliable choice of weapon for those who can master its particulars. </text>
<text> Greatsword forged from golden-hued meteoric ore. The blade conceals gravity-manipulating magic. A weapon unique to the Onyx Lords, a race of ancients with skin of stone who were said to have risen to life when a meteor struck long ago. </text>
<text> This curved greatsword wielded by the brawny sellswords of Kaiden combines the blade of a scimitar with the heft of a hatchet. A difficult to handle weapon that demands much of the wielder's strength and dexterity, but with practice and ability, it can serve as a versatile weapon even on horseback. </text>
<text> Curved greatsword with a gently undulating blade wielded by Bloodhound Knights. A fearsome blade capable of brutal airborne attacks. </text>
<text> Curved greatsword wielded by Magma Wyrms. The shape resembles a dragon's jaw and is covered in hard scales. It's said these land-bound dragons were once humans heroes who partook in dragon communion, a grave transgression for which they were cursed to crawl the earth upon their bellies, shadows of their former selves. </text>
<text> Weapon wielded by the knights of Zamor who earned great renown during the War against the Giants. In apparent devotion to winter, the curved blade is styled after an icy wind and imbued with a powerful frost effect. </text>
<text> Heavy-bladed curved sword of colossal size awarded to Omen as a tool of war. This weapon is made to take advantage of brute strength. The pattern etched upon the blade is the remnant of a deteriorative malediction. Indeed, when bestowing a weapon, preparations must be made for taking it away. </text>
<text> Curved sword with a flickering flame motif. Wielded by the Fire Monks who came from the Mountaintops of the Giants. The monks came to the land of Liurnia in pursuit of a fugitive who stole their fire. </text>
<text> Curved greatsword of colossal size forged of dull iron and wielded by the beastmen of Farum Azula. The blade is incredibly heavy, but well-balanced. Comparatively easy to wield for the damage it delivers. It's clear the beastmen possess knowledge beyond human ken. </text>
<text> Warped blade of shifting hue used by Morgott, the Omen King. The accursed blood that Morgott recanted and sealed away reformed into this blade. </text>
<text> Large katana used by Monks of the Giants' Flame. The characteristic blade has the motif of flickering flames. </text>
<text> A katana with a long single-edged curved blade. A unique weapon wielded by the samurai from the Land of Reeds. The blade, with its undulating design, boasts extraordinary sharpness, and its slash attacks cause blood loss. </text>
<text> Katana with a ferociously long blade. Signature weapon of Yura, hunter of Bloody Fingers. Reminiscent of a reinforced spear, its imposing length can be put to good use with powerful thrusting attacks. </text>
<text> Blade built into Malenia's prosthetic arm. Through consecration it is resistant to rot. Malenia's war prosthesis symbolized her victories. Some claim to have seen wings when the weapon was raised aloft; wings of fierce determination that have never known defeat. </text>
<text> Katana forged from meteoric ore to dispatch lifeforms born of falling stars. Deals magic damage. The blade is weighty, known to deliver slashes of such ferocity that the impact is said to resemble the crash of a falling meteor. </text>
<text> Weapon of Okina, swordsman from the Land of Reeds. A cursed weapon that has felled countless men. When Mohg, the Lord of Blood, first felt Okina's sword, and madness, upon his flesh, he had a proposal, to offer Okina the life of a demon, whose thirst would never go unsated. </text>
<text> Katana forged of glintstone. Masterpiece of a Sellian swordsmith. Light enwreathes the blade when sheathed, explaining its Moonveil moniker. </text>
<text> A weapon made by sharpening a Gravel Stone scale, thought to be the source of ancient dragon immortality, into an unclouded blade. Alas, the Dragonkin Soldiers never attained immortality, and perished as decrepit, pale imitations of their skyborn kin. </text>
<text> Sinister katana modeled after a serpent bone. The densely packed row of spines that jut away from the cutting edge are coated in a lethal poison. </text>
<text> A sword with blades on both sides of the hilt. This weapon is difficult to wield and demands high dexterity. Can be wielded with a single hand, but its true strength is unlocked with dual-handed spinning attacks. </text>
<text> Unique twinblade wielded by Godskin Apostles characterized by its disturbing design. One end features a sickle for slicing attacks while the other boasts a winding spike for boring into flesh. Much skill is required to wield this weapon due to its asymmetric nature. </text>
<text> An attractive twinblade of fine make that prizes the chivalric way. Can be wielded with a single hand, but its true strength is unlocked with dual-handed spinning attacks. </text>
<text> Twinned naginata forged in the Land of Reeds. Chosen weapon of Eleonora, Violet Bloody Finger. Her mastery of the sword was such that her onslaught was likened to a whirlwind, but now her legacy is stained by accursed blood. </text>
<text> Bronze twinblade wielded by Valiant Gargoyle. Just like the wielder, the missing parts have been mended with corpse wax; a patchwork of champions. </text>
<text> Bronze twinblade wielded by Valiant Gargoyle, mended with blackened corpse wax. Deals holy damage. Such is the mark of those who serve Maliketh, the Black Blade. </text>
<text> An iron bludgeon with sharp protrusions. Striking attacks have few drawbacks, potent as they are at breaking through guards and stances. Most suited to head on slugging matches. </text>
<text> A thick, solid lump of wood. Wielding this striking weapon requires no skill. A simple, primitive weapon that requires only brute strength and persistence to hammer your foe into the ground. </text>
<text> Hard, curved club, shaped like a crescent moon. Wielded instead of a curved sword by Albinaurics lacking dexterity. The only point of similarity between the two is the shape. </text>
<text> Warhammer with a hard protruding beak. A pickaxe designed for combat, in essence. A simple but highly effective weapon, the weighty piercing attack casually rips through metal armor. </text>
<text> Warhammer comprised of a globe attached to a handle. Though a bludgeon dealing strike damage, the appellative star is covered in spikes which cause blood loss. Ironic given its graceful name, this weapon often reeks of blood. </text>
<text> A steel mace resembling a charming bouquet of roses. Each petal has a sharpened edge, leaving the roses perpetually colored with blood. This weapon reflects White Mask Varré's manner of speech rather well, enticing in its splendor, but full of deadly consequence. </text>
<text> A club with beast fangs wrapped around the striking end. The uneven spread of fangs causes blood loss. Given only to the toughest of demi-humans, this weapon is a badge of honor. Or so the demi-humans believe. </text>
<text> Hammer comprised of a large stone affixed to a metal handle. Originally a blacksmith's tool. The art of smithing is said to have originated among the giants. This weapon's striking attacks boast ample weight behind them. </text>
<text> Warhammer made to resemble flickering flames. Signature weapon of the Fire Monks, who hail from the Mountaintops of the Giants. The unique strong attack rouses fiery combative spirit. </text>
<text> Golden horn of the Oracle Envoys. Profoundly weighty, its blows are sure to be felt. Originally an instrument, but one that cannot be sounded by a mere human. Or perhaps it is too early to sound the call. </text>
<text> Scepter in the form of a hand grasping a pearl. Signature weapon of Sir Gideon Ofnir, the All-Knowing. The pearl stands for the world, the heavens, and an eye, representing the many forms of knowledge, never fully attainable. Even knowing that, the All-Knowing's hand grasps for it. </text>
<text> Mace shaped like a suspended metal droplet wielded by monks of the Eternal City. Forged from liquid metal from a Silver Tear, it is thoroughly tempered until hardened. </text>
<text> Bludgeon made of an enormous finger sheathed in several heavy rings. Thought to have been cut from an ancestor of the Fingercreeper. Some life yet remains in this legacy of an ancient act of blasphemy, as evidenced by the barely perceptible warmth it still exudes. </text>
<text> Signature weapon of battlemages, hewn from hard glintstone. This club is much heavier than its size suggests, but has no magic power. So that they not lose sight of the true essence of combat, battlemages prefer to feel the impact of their blows, fighting their opponents hand to hand. </text>
<text> Stone hammer made in the lands of the Numen, outside the Lands Between. The tool with which Queen Marika shattered the Elden Ring and Radagon attempted to repair it. The hammer partially broke upon shattering the Ring, becoming splintered with rune fragments. </text>
<text> A thick, solid lump of wood. Wielding this striking weapon requires no skill. A simple, primitive weapon that requires only brute strength to swing about. </text>
<text> Huge thick horn carved with tree ring-like markings adapted into a bludgeoning weapon. Wielded by ancestral follower warriors. The ancient horn is imbued with the power of ancestral spirits. A small amount of HP is restored upon defeating an enemy. </text>
<text> Large iron warhammer designed for gladiatorial combat. Used by duelists who were exiled from the colosseum. Weighty enough to crush armor and its wearer alike. </text>
<text> Huge bludgeon with sharp protrusions. An enlarged version of its smaller cousin. Maintains all the advantages of smaller bludgeons, boasting few deficiencies while being very capable at breaking enemy guards and stances. A shrewd choice for simple slugging matches. </text>
<text> Large curved club of hard wood, shaped like a crescent moon. Wielded by Albinaurics lacking the dexterity demanded by a curved sword, and who prefer the added weight and destructive force. </text>
<text> Large bludgeon decorated with flowers and many-colored fabrics. Ceremonial tool used by dancers during the festivities of Dominula, Windmill Village. The striking end is a skull too large in size to be human. Grants trace amounts of runes on landing attacks. </text>
<text> Large pickaxe designed to crack thick bedrock. Tool of sturdy miners. Not originally designed as a weapon, but very adept at piercing armor. "Little wretches, do you think your armor harder than stone?" </text>
<text> Greathammer with a striking end modelled to resemble five beastly claws. The black nails protruding from golden fur are said to represent Serosh, Lord of Beasts, who went on to become King Godfrey's Regent. </text>
<text> Long golden horn of the Oracle Envoys. Profoundly weighty, its blows are sure to be felt. Originally an instrument, but one that cannot be sounded by a mere human. Or perhaps it is too early to sound the call. </text>
<text> Candlestand used in worship of Birac, the most hallowed Monk Prelate of the Giants' Flame. Concerned over the lazy arrogance with which the monks treated the Flame, Birac severed his own head as a lesson to the others, intending it be used as a candlestand. His faith yet smolders from within the cranial vessel. </text>
<text> Huge bludgeon with three stars at the striking end. Though primarily a striking weapon, the stars' spikes cause blood loss. A blood-stained star is an ill omen, a fact not lost upon those against whom this weapon is brought to bear. Landing attacks slightly restores HP. </text>
<text> Weapon made from an ordinary stone brick. Wielded by a laborer who lead a rebellion, and later become a champion himself. Even among other bludgeons of its size, this weapon is especially weighty. The strength of a giant is required to wield it. </text>
<text> Scepter in the shape of a serpent devouring the world. This weapon will one day become the very symbol of the Lord of Blasphemy. One of the legendary armaments. A vision of the future briefly seen by Rykard in his final moments before being devoured by the great serpent. </text>
<text> Large iron warhammer designed for gladiatorial combat, now festering with scarlet rot. Weighty enough to crush armor and its wearer alike. </text>
<text> A flail with two additional bludgeoning heads. Weapon of the Night's Cavalry who ride funeral steeds. The large spikes make it highly effective at inducing blood loss, but also demand higher dexterity to wield. </text>
<text> Weapon consisting of a bludgeoning head attached to a handle by a chain. The iron ball is spiked and induces blood loss. Blows from this weapon cannot be parried. The charge attack whirls the iron ball around for increased force before striking. </text>
<text> Three bludgeoning copper heads attached to a handle by chains. Signature weapon of Necromancer Garris, the heretical sage. The heads were made to resemble those of his wife and two children. </text>
<text> Flail which deals magic damage, having been imbued with power by the remembrance of Astel. Formed of the same many-colored star debris that comprised the form of the Naturalborn of the Void. </text>
<text> A spiked iron tube attached by a chain wielded by Mad Pumpkin Heads. Especially large for a flail, wielding it requires more strength than it does dexterity. </text>
<text> A thick, heavy blade attached to a handle. A versatile, standard weapon Capable of powerful attacks thanks to the weighty blade, these weapons are also regarded for their powerful charge attacks. </text>
<text> Peculiar hatchet wielded by imps. The gently undulating forked blade is known as an "imp's tongue" and causes blood loss. </text>
<text> Commonly known as a hatchet, this smaller variety of axe is an everyday work tool. Despite its short reach, it is easy to handle, exceling in successive attacks. </text>
<text> Axe made from a herbivore's skull. Weapon of the ancestral followers who disdain metal. This axe is more of a bludgeon; it forgoes a bladed edge, instead using the beast's molar teeth to buffet foes, dealing strike damage. </text>
<text> Fairly large iron cleaver, commonly used by the maltreated Misbegotten. Steeped in resentment, these weapons are swung wildly and relentlessly, often after rushing up to foes. </text>
<text> Unique weapon wielded by young Albinaurics, this sword is modelled after the ripples that are thought to be the origin of their species. Its attack power is greatly enhanced with one's arcane attribute. </text>
<text> Cleaver decorated with many-colored fabrics. Ceremonial tool used by dancers during the festivities of Dominula, Windmill Village. Crafted from human bone. Grants trace amounts of runes upon landing attacks. </text>
<text> A hatchet with a frost-coated blade. One of several gifts given by Castle Sol in the distant north. Known as "freezing fog," the blade is thought to be a dragon's scale. Inflicts a powerful frost effect. </text>
<text> Single-sided axe used by the warriors of the highlands. Brave combatants begin battle by crying out their names. Roars are enhanced by this weapon. </text>
<text> Hatchet used in ancient sacrificial rite. A Deathbird is depicted as a malevolent deity. The power of the rite yet lingers. A small amount of FP is restored upon slaying a foe. </text>
<text> Usher of Death, Rosus, who shows the path to the catacombs throughout the Lands Between, is depicted on this ritual axe. The dead easily lose their way, and have always been in sore need of a guiding hand. </text>
<text> Battle axe designed to resemble a hawk, with its wings comprising the blade. Signature weapon of warriors who strive to remain one with the storm, despite being so far from their place of birth. Their hearts are proud, and thereby easily undone. </text>
<text> Greataxe akin to a huge lump of iron. Recognized as the weapon of choice of badland chieftains. Too heavy to be wielded by those of merely ordinary strength, blows from this axe will flatten enemies, and the force of its charged attack is a sight to behold. </text>
<text> Oversized double-headed axe with a bizarre, almost melted appearance. Brute strength is the only thing required to wield this weapon, which appears to have taken quite the beating itself. </text>
<text> The blade of this huge, loathsome cleaver comprises a row of amputated Omen horns. Weapon of slaughter wielded by Omenkillers.  The hideous horns cause blood loss, adding vibrant colors to the ongoing mayhem. </text>
<text> Greataxe with a large, arcing blade and long handle. The "Crescent Moon" of its name is said to have been spurred by nostalgia. Specializes in sweeping through foes by making use of its long handle. </text>
<text> Greataxe wielded by Godrick the Grafted. This golden battleaxe is emblazoned with the figure of a beast, representing the strength of Godfrey, First Elden Lord and patriarch of the golden lineage. "I command thee kneel! For I am the lord of all that is golden!" </text>
<text> Large iron axe with a long handle. Weapon of the maltreated Misbegotten. Making use of the force generated by its length, this weapon's resentment-charged blows are difficult to stop. </text>
<text> A rusty anchor wielded as a weapon. Each of its four flukes is thick and sharp, enabling piercing attacks. When the Tarnished left the Lands Between with their Lord, one boat alone was said to have been left behind. </text>
<text> Bulky cleaver welded to a long haft. Said to have been used to dispatch the remnants of defeated armies, felling them like timber. Perhaps that is the reason it excels at critical hits. </text>
<text> A unique horn in which the power of ancestral spirits fiercely dwells, this large, wing-shaped specimen is wielded as a weapon of spirit worship. In the ancestral spirit-worshipping faith, these are considered envoys' wings, made to reap the lives of beings which experience no sprouting. </text>
<text> Huge carving knife made to cleanly butcher the human body. Signature weapon of the Ogress Anastasia, known to have eaten countless Tarnished while disguised as a Finger Maiden. Restores a very small amount of HP when it squarely strikes an enemy. </text>
<text> Bronze greataxe wielded by Valiant Gargoyle. Just like the wielder, the missing parts have been mended with corpse wax; a patchwork of champions. </text>
<text> Bronze greataxe wielded by Valiant Gargoyle, mended with blackened corpse wax. Deals holy damage. Such is the mark of those who serve Maliketh, the Black Blade. </text>
<text> A exceedingly plain spear of modest weight. Simple to wield compared to many of its peers, strong attack unleashes a series of successive piercing thrusts. </text>
<text> Weapon comprised of a blade attached to a long haft. A far-reaching piercing weapon, it can be wielded from behind the safety of a raised shield. Very effective against mounted foes. </text>
<text> Spear fashioned from pure crystal; a deed impossible for a human. Enwreathed with powerful magic, its attack scales with intelligence. The inscrutable Crystalians have but one clear purpose; to safeguard their crystals unto the end. One theory posits that they yearn for the return of their creator who will carve for them new brethren. </text>
<text> Harpoon with a tip made from a sharpened meteorite shard. Wielded by the claymen who infest dynastic remains. The blade emits a faint light and deals magic damage. </text>
<text> Spear of the Cleanrot Knights who fought alongside Malenia, Blade of Miquella. The winged golden blade deals holy damage. The diminutive shield is blessed with an incantation that wards off rot. </text>
<text> Spear with a wide tip. In addition to its thrusting attacks, this highly versatile weapon can be swung to sweep through foes. </text>
<text> Rake decorated with many-colored fabrics. Ceremonial tool used by dancers during the festivities of Dominula, Windmill Village. Crafted from human bone. Grants trace amounts of runes upon landing attacks. </text>
<text> A longspear featuring an especially lengthy handle. Specialized for use from long distances, it boasts the longest reach of any melee weapon. Incredibly useful even against foes on horseback, but hard to wield in cramped spaces. </text>
<text> Torch fastened to a long pole. Lights up dark areas, but cannot be raised overhead. Used by soldiers on watch, its attacks set foes aflame. </text>
<text> Spear whittled from the weapon wielded by Gransax. One of the legendary armaments. A great ancient dragon, Gransax once rained calamity upon the Royal Capital—the only time in historical record that Leyndell's walls have fallen. This marked the dawn of the war against the ancient dragons. </text>
<text> Weapon consisting of a three-pronged blade affixed to a long pole. The long central blade closely resembles a katana. A weapon of the Land of Reeds, known for its ability to be wielded as a spear while still being capable of performing slashing attacks. </text>
<text> Ritual spear used by priests of old who were permitted to come among the Deathbirds. The priests became guardians of the birds through the rite of Death, which also serves as an oath sworn to their distant resurrection. </text>
<text> Instrument of torture used on nobles behind the curtain at the Volcano Manor of Mt. Gelmir. Its numerous spikes pierce the flesh, then singe the wounds with flame. The smell of burnt blood induces despair in the victim. A candlestick conceived by a thorough mind. </text>
<text> Weapon comprised of a spiked cylinder attached to a long pole. Capable of dealing strike damage when swung. The spikes induce blood loss. Weapon of the Marionette Soldiers employed by sorcerers. </text>
<text> Commonly used iron spear with no notable traits. The blade is severely rusted. </text>
<text> Spear fashioned from pure crystal; a deed impossible for a human. Enwreathed with powerful magic, its attack scales with intelligence. Though festering with scarlet rot, its magic remains potent. </text>
<text> Trident of Mohg, Lord of Blood. A sacred spear that will come to symbolize his dynasty. As well as serving as a weapon, it is an instrument of communion with an outer god who bestows power upon accursed blood. The mother of truth desires a wound. </text>
<text> Siluria's Tree, weapon of one of the two honored as foremost among the Crucible Knights. The primordial form of the Erdtree is close in nature to life itself, and this spear, modeled on its crucible, is imbued with ancient holy essence. </text>
<text> Weapon that serves as both greatsword and spear. Thought to have been used to hunt an immortal great serpent in the distant past, it manifests a long blade of light when facing such a creature. When their master's heroic aspirations degenerated into mere greed, his men searched for a weapon with which they might halt their lord. </text>
<text> War spear singed and blistered by fingers, used by Vyke, Knight of the Roundtable Hold. Like Vyke himself, it has been tormented by the yellow flame of frenzy from within. </text>
<text> Considered a type of greatspear, this weapon has no blade, but instead features a long, conical body designed to pierce. Though heavy and hard to wield, this weapon displays its worth in horseback combat whether mounted or even on foot. </text>
<text> Golden spear with tree-like design. Wielded by knights employed as palace guards in the Royal Capital of Leyndell. Deals holy damage. Requiring superior dexterity to wield, this greatspear can perform consecutive thrust attacks despite its larger size. </text>
<text> A long-handled polearm that combines the functions of both axe and spear. Can be used to press a single enemy with continuous thrusting attacks, or swept at groups, taking advantage of its great reach and cleaving blade. A versatile weapon for any situation. </text>
<text> Glaive made from a hard, sharpened shell. Wielded by the pests who emerged from the Swamp of Aeonia. Slightly increases non-physical damage negation. Though men might recognize the keen intellect of the pests evidenced by this spear's uncanny design, it will never be understood by them. </text>
<text> This polearm features a hard, sharpened beak-like spike attached to its head, designed to pierce armor. Though designed mainly as a thrusting weapon, its long handle can be utilized to get around an enemy's guard with a sideward sweeping attack. </text>
<text> A finely-crafted halberd intricately engraved with an ancient motif. Given to knights who, whether by misfortune or misdeed, were forced to abandon their homes. Most of these knights were sent to the fringes, where they were forced to start anew with only despair for company. </text>
<text> A beaten red battle standard is furled around this time-worn halberd. Even after his lord was fled, Commander O'Neil continued to brandish this flag in the devastation of the rot-eaten field of battle, the sole veteran who remembers this battle with pride. </text>
<text> A jet-black glaive with a blade as weighty as a bludgeon. Weapon of the Night's Cavalry who ride funeral steeds. This glaive excels at weighty slash attacks that crash into foes, making it a powerful weapon even on horseback. </text>
<text> Weapon wielded by young Albinaurics. The blade is said to resemble a partial image of a ripple, and its attack power scales with one's arcane attribute. </text>
<text> A weapon comprised of a saw blade attached to a long grip. Brandished by the vulgar militia, its serrated edge is very effective at inflicting blood loss. The saw is said to also be used to cut up bodies to feed the militia, but there are no firsthand witnesses to confirm the dire rumor. </text>
<text> Weighty halberd forged of gold. Wielded by the Order of Tree Sentinels, heavily equipped knights. Deals holy damage. A masterfully crafted weapon that lives up to its heft, but is difficult for one of mere human strength to wield. </text>
<text> Weapon comprised of a sharp blade affixed to a long grip. It is in fact a sickle repurposed to be a tool of war. This far-reaching weapon excels at slashing attacks. </text>
<text> Intricately crafted silver war sickle wielded by Loretta, Knight of the Haligtree. Originally given for service as a personal guard to Carian royalty, the weapon's blue glintstone has been replaced with unalloyed gold. </text>
<text> Weapon comprising a long handle and broad blade sharpened from the hard wood of old trees. Wielded by guardians of the Minor Erdtrees, known as experts in the arts of combat. The power of this weapon scales greatly with dexterity. </text>
<text> A hooked blade attached to a long handle. Wielded by the vulgar militia, its attacks can slip through an enemy's guard. The vulgar militia are the undecorated stewards of rancid, scorched battlefields that none dare approach, and forbidden domains better forgotten by the rest of the world. </text>
<text> Halberd shaped like a dragon, enwreathed with both ice and lightning. Alas, the Dragonkin Soldiers never attained immortality, and perished as decrepit, pale imitations of their skyborn kin. </text>
<text> Bronze halberd wielded by Valiant Gargoyle. Just like the wielder, the missing parts have been mended with corpse wax; a patchwork of champions. </text>
<text> Bronze halberd wielded by Valiant Gargoyle, mended with blackened corpse wax. Deals holy damage. Such is the mark of those who serve Maliketh, the Black Blade. </text>
<text> Large scythe featuring a long, slender blade. Designed to reap, this weapon is capable of rapidly inflicting blood loss while also slipping through an enemy's guard. In the hands of a highly dexterous wielder it is capable of striking fear into the heart of any foe. </text>
<text> Greatscythe comprised of a large blade affixed to a crooked stick. Weapon wielded by the aged grave keepers who tend the forgotten graveyards throughout the Lands Between. This weapon is said to have served as a charm against evil spirits in times of old. </text>
<text> War scythe of the Cleanrot Knights who fought alongside Malenia, Blade of Miquella. This was the weapon of commanders in Malenia's army, and the half-halo blade deals holy damage. </text>
<text> Sacred scythe resembling a pair of white wings. Deals holy damage. According to pagan belief, white-winged maidens are said to be Death's gentle envoys. </text>
<text> A leather whip. Not originally used for combat, but as an instrument of pain. Though its supple attacks cannot be thwarted by parrying or even guarding, it is incapable of dealing critical hits. </text>
<text> Hefty whip covered in crimson thorns. Weapon of the Prelates who lead the Fire Monks. A device of fearsome religious encouragement, it is fashioned in the image of the briars of sin. Very effective at inflicting blood loss. </text>
<text> This ritual implement is a three pronged candlestick with solid flames formed of the magma of Mt. Gelmir. When wielded as a weapon, the flames become supple whips of lava. </text>
<text> Metal whip formed of razor-sharp chain-link blades that have the appearance of flower petals. This work of art is handed down through the generations of the illustrious House Hoslow. High dexterity is required to wield this weapon, but it excels at inflicting devastating blood loss. "The tale of House Hoslow is told in blood." </text>
<text> Hefty whip woven from the flame-red hair of a Fire Giant. Every giant is red of hair, and Radagon was said to have despised his own red locks. Perhaps that was a curse of their kind. </text>
<text> This weapon made of extremely thin, flexible blades of metal is wielded like a whip by Nightfolk warriors. Though in essence a whip with a cutting edge, it can also be used as a spear to pierce foes. </text>
<text> A weapon built for striking with the fists, made of tough leather inlaid with iron rivets. Fist weapons come in pairs, and two-handing this weapon will equip it to both hands. </text>
<text> A caestus with the rivets replaced by blood loss-inducing spikes. Fist weapons come in pairs, and two-handing this weapon will equip it to both hands. </text>
<text> The embodiment of the power that still remained in the dragon's head that was grafted to Godrick's left arm. The wielder's arm will take the form of a small dragon, sprouting sharp dragon fangs at the fist. This weapon cannot be two-handed. </text>
<text> Iron manifer of spherical shape. Big Boggart the blackguard's weapon of choice. Not a weapon to be taken lightly, as its weighty blows shatter bones with ease. </text>
<text> Spherical iron manifer covered in spikes which induce blood loss. Used in brutal games of pugilism. </text>
<text> Imported dagger design with a rather unique handle. The blade can be swung about as the extension of one's fist. </text>
<text> Horrific weapon made of a hardened skeletal arm. Wielded by Ensha of the Royal Remains. Fitted by placing one's hands into the fists' grips until they dig in. "O clinging creature. A king relinquishes not the hand." </text>
<text> Bladed prosthetic leg enwreathed with the power of lightning, instead attached to the fist. Commander Niall, veteran of Castle Sol, offered this prosthesis in exchange for the lives of defeated knights held prisoner. He went on to lead these men as an army of no nation. </text>
<text> One of the weapons originating from the Two Fingers. A formless sequence of ciphers comprise its blade, and as such no shield can repel it. Deals holy damage. The furtive inscription appears to hang in the air; the language of light spoken by the Two Fingers. </text>
<text> Weapon worn on the fist comprised of sharp parallel blades favored by those who lurk in the dark. Lacerations cause blood loss with great effect. Claw weapons come in pairs, and two-handing this weapon will equip it to both hands. </text>
<text> One of the weapons designed for gladiatorial combat. Used by duelists who were exiled from the colosseum. The black fang protruding from the bronze snake head is coated in deadly poison. </text>
<text> Large curved claws used by Bloodhound Knights. The curve allows the weapon to slip through an enemy's guard. </text>
<text> Claw comprised of two sharp, thin blades. Wielded by the assassins of ravenmount, this weapon allows them to imitate the attacks of Deathbirds. Besides excelling at airborne attacks, its charge attack mimics the vicious swoop of a bird of prey. </text>
<text> Colossal hammer with the appearance of roiling flames. Weapon of the Prelates who lead the Fire Monks. Its heft represents the weight of their guardianship. The hammer's head is unusually substantial, and strong attacks will fling foes into the air. </text>
<text> Large stone staff embedded with glintstone. Wielded by Erdtree Burial Watchdogs who protect catacombs. The Watchdogs, battered and broken over their lengthy tenure, rule the catacombs and are even said to command the imps. </text>
<text> An enormous club of hard wood. Wildly hammering foes with this striking weapon requires no dexterity; only brute force. While it may seem sacrilegious, this weapon is said to be a withered branch of the Erdtree. Imbued with holy power, this weapon will never snap. </text>
<text> Fanned golden horn of the Oracle Envoys. Profoundly weighty, its blows are sure to be felt. Originally an instrument, but one that cannot be sounded by a mere human. Or perhaps it is too early to sound the call. </text>
<text> Greataxe designed for gladiatorial combat. Used by duelists who were exiled from the colosseum. A weapon reserved for duelist champions, the charge attack is particularly ferocious. </text>
<text> Weapon of Godfrey, Elden Lord. It was broken in a battle fought as leader of the Tarnished during the Long March. This weapon is symbolic of Godfrey's vow to conduct himself as a lord, later becoming an emblem of the golden lineage. In the days of the past, a crown was warranted with strength. </text>
<text> Weapon said to have been whittled from the claw of a great, ancient dragon, wielded by grotesque Tree Sentinels who yet serve the Erdtree. The claw is enwreathed with lightning, and tears through the dragons' feeble descendants with ease. </text>
<text> Ceremonial staff depicting the Erdtree in its historic radiance. Wielded by the avatars who protect the Minor Erdtrees. The avatars, emerging in the wake of the Elden Ring's shattering, were determined to protect the withering Erdtree's offspring. </text>
<text> Part of a Fallingstar Beast's jaw, hard and shining black, fashioned into a weapon. With its sharp point, this colossal weapon can skewer foes. </text>
<text> Great iron wheel lined with flesh-flaying blades. Device of torture used by Inquisitor Ghiza. As the wheel spins it causes severe pain and blood loss. The design was adopted for use as the iconic weapon wielded by Iron Virgins. </text>
<text> A hammer made from a boulder, used in the War against the Giants. One of the heftiest weapons in the entire Lands Between. After the giants were quelled, and man turned against man in violence, this weapon was all but forgotten. Man has grown feeble in comparison to his forebears. </text>
<text> A great halberd of black stone crafted by a civilization now gone to ruin. Wielded by the Guardian Golem. </text>
<text> Mining tool of stonedigger trolls used to crack bedrock. Trolls are descended from the giants, and these were supposedly once used as ceremonial smithing tools. In the distant past, smithing was considered divine. </text>
<text> Ceremonial staff depicting the Erdtree in its historic radiance. It festers with scarlet rot. Wielded by the avatars who protect the Minor Erdtrees. </text>
<text> Greataxe designed for gladiatorial combat, now festering with scarlet rot. Used by duelists who were exiled from the colosseum. </text>
<text> This torch's tip is wrapped in oil-soaked rags and set on fire. The flame can illuminate dark locales, or be used to attack enemies. Can be raised up when equipped in the left hand, illuminating more of the surrounding area. </text>
<text> Torch wound with metal wire. The flame can illuminate dark locales, or be used to attack enemies. Heavier than a normal torch, but the heated filament boosts fire damage dealt. </text>
<text> Candlestand torch that burns with a light-purple flame. The carvings depict St. Trina, but in adult form, somewhat unnervingly. The light-purple flame induces sleep. </text>
<text> Metal torch that burns with cold ghostflame. Tool of the Fallen Hawks who prowl the underground rivers. When the band's last embers were used up in their long search, they began to burn the bones of their fellows, acquiring the cold ghostflame, but sealing their fate as dwellers of the underground for all eternity. </text>
<text> A torch which burns oil infused with a special incense. The aroma pacifies wild beasts. Torches such as these were used to keep unwelcome beasts away from treasure troves hidden in caves. </text>
<text> Torch given to protectors of the Erdtree. Its flames are bestowed with a special incantation which allows the bearer to see assassins cloaked in veils. Furnished on behalf of the Erdtree and the Grace-Given Lord such that a Night of Black Knives will never come again. </text>
<text> A small metal roundshield. The bump in the center is designed to parry. A well-timed parry deflects an enemy's attack, breaking their stance and leaving them open to a critical hit. Though risk is inherent, this shield favors aggression. </text>
<text> Golden shield used by the perfumers of Leyndell during military service. Made to be thin and light of weight, even those lacking strength can employ this immunity-boosting shield. </text>
<text> Small copper dome-shaped roundshield carried by the man-serpents of Mt. Gelmir. Said to have been tempered in lava, it boasts great resistance to fire. </text>
<text> A creaky old wooden shield, circular in shape. Roughly reinforced with vines. There are countless other shields available of better make. This piece of scrap isn't worth the effort of equipping. </text>
<text> Pillory made to punish serious felons, used as a shield. Though made of good, sturdy wood, it is only a makeshift tool and performs as such. Perhaps due to its use as a device with which the guilty were made to endure prolonged suffering, it raises vitality. </text>
<text> Shield fashioned from a tall broken jar carried by the beastmen of Farum Azula. There is a particular knack to wielding it. The beastmen have always fired earthenware jars for the express purpose of making shields. Such are their ways, strange though they are. </text>
<text> A small, wooden roundshield. It is light and easy to handle, but cannot offer the damage negation of a metal shield. Its emblem is an ancient thorn design. Though it isn't much, it boosts fire damage negation. </text>
<text> A small, wooden roundshield. It is light and easy to handle, but cannot offer the damage negation of a metal shield. An ancient cipher engraving lines the circumference. Though it isn't much, it boosts holy damage negation. </text>
<text> Small wooden roundshield that has been reinforced with metal. It is light and easy to handle, but cannot offer the damage negation of a true metal shield. The design riveted to the center represents both sword and tree. </text>
<text> Small wooden roundshield that has been reinforced with metal. It is light and easy to handle, but cannot offer the damage negation of a true metal shield. The design is said to represent the stars of the night sky, portending fate. </text>
<text> Small metal roundshield depicting a sinister rift. An antiquated charm that glares back at an enemy, it boosts focus. </text>
<text> An ordinary small roundshield made of metal. Heavier than a wooden shield, but boasts higher damage negation. Finely balanced, this shield is easy to use. </text>
<text> Small metal roundshield. Heavier than a wooden shield, but boasts higher damage negation. Though the gold leaf is peeling and the effect is slight, it still boosts holy damage negation. </text>
<text> Small metal roundshield. Heavier than a wooden shield, but boasts higher damage negation. The ice crest originates from a Carian princess. Though the effect is slight, it boosts magic damage negation and resistance to frost. </text>
<text> Small shield made upon Mt. Gelmir forged from uncooling lava. Resists frost with its heat, and can even be used to deal fire damage if wielded as a weapon. </text>
<text> Small shield of antlers arranged in an eddy-like pattern. If used to attack a foe, the shield's antlers inflict blood loss. Once given to a Tarnished warrior who cultivated close ties to the ancestral followers. Though the effect is only slight, it boosts immunity, robustness, and focus. </text>
<text> Armament designed for gladiatorial combat. Rises above its peers as a particularly showy specimen. The sculpted bronze snake is a poisonous breed, boosting the wielder's resistance to poison. </text>
<text> A standard medium-sized metal shield. Metal shields reliably negate physical damage when guarding, a trait which made them highly trusted on the battlefield. </text>
<text> Leather shield of Stormveil soldiers. Much like the castle, it is marred by mottling and thorns. Some say it is the curse of grafting which causes such affliction, while others talk of its root being something altogether more sinister hidden deep within the castle. </text>
<text> Wooden shield of Stormveil soldiers. Much like the castle, it is marred by mottling and thorns. Some say it is the curse of grafting which causes such affliction, while others talk of its root being something altogether more sinister hidden deep within the castle. </text>
<text> A tall medium-sized metal shield. Given to knights who, whether by misfortune or misdeed, were forced to abandon their homes. Most of these knights were sent to the fringes, where they were forced to start anew with only despair for company. </text>
<text> Tall oval shield made of metal carried by young Albinaurics. The ornamentation represents the primordial drop of dew from which they are said to have been created. Boasts exceptional magic damage negation. The Albinaurics' most formidable foes were sorcerers, after all. </text>
<text> Shield of honor depicting a city crowned by the sun. It has seen better days. Much like the wear upon the shield, the Seat of the Sun is long faded away. </text>
<text> Shield of radiant silver, festooned with amber and carried by Loretta, Knight of the Haligtree. The shape is said to imitate that of a sacred drop of dew, which inspired the absurd rumor that Loretta herself was an Albinauric. </text>
<text> A wooden roundshield that has been reinforced with metal. Comparatively light for its size, this shield is easy to handle but lacks a true metal shield's ability to negate damage. </text>
<text> A standard medium-sized metal shield. Highly reputed for its solid build and reliability. Emblazoned with a yellow scorpion, a warning of surprise attacks and sudden strikes. </text>
<text> Shield featuring a vividly painted twinbird. The twinbird is said to be the envoy of an outer god, and mother of the Deathbirds. At dwindling levels of HP, this shield slightly boosts both attack and defense. </text>
<text> A standard medium-sized metal shield. Highly reputed for its solid build and reliability. The design represents the Erdtree foregrounded against a blue sky. </text>
<text> On the larger side for a medium-sized shield, the face has been covered in brass. Commonly employed in the Shattering. </text>
<text> Shield fashioned from a great turtle shell. The natural curve helps it contend with foes' attacks. The turtle is a symbol of tirelessness, and this shield boosts stamina recovery speed. </text>
<text> Shield made to venerate a maiden whose eyes were crushed by Briars of Sin before being reborn in these lands. Venerating the repose of the soul, this shield boosts focus. The briars can be used to attack foes. </text>
<text> A teardrop-shaped, medium-sized shield embedded with blue glintstones. Carried by knights who served the Carian royal family. Excels when facing magic or holy attacks. Just who were these knights preparing to fight? </text>
<text> A roundshield covered in leather. On the larger side for a medium-sized shield. Though its damage negation may be lacking compared to a metal shield, it can handle a wider range of attack affinities. </text>
<text> A tall, medium-sized wooden shield. Light for its size, and easy to handle. The circular horsehead design evokes a swift gallop. </text>
<text> A tall, medium-sized wooden shield. Light for its size, and easy to handle. Thought to represent a surreptitious prophecy of cardinal sin, the lit candle-tree design was forbidden. </text>
<text> A tall, medium-sized wooden shield. Light for its size, and easy to handle. Carried by soldiers of the village that is afflicted by frenzy. The yellow flame is the symbol of the affliction, serving as a warning to those who might approach the village. </text>
<text> A tall, medium-sized wooden shield. Light for its size, and easy to handle. Adorned with a long-forgotten crest of Stormveil, ancient in design. </text>
<text> A medium-sized metal shield. Easier to handle than a kite shield. Features a beast as its crest, serving to remind warriors not to succumb to the arousal of battle. Fight with passion, but become not its prisoner. </text>
<text> A medium-sized metal shield. Easier to handle than a kite shield. The crest symbolizes red wings. </text>
<text> A medium-sized metal shield. Easier to handle than a kite shield. The crest represents a forest and river. </text>
<text> A medium-sized metal shield. Easier to handle than a kite shield. The sun in eclipse is said to be the symbol of the Wandering Mausoleum where the soulless demigods slumber. </text>
<text> A medium-sized metal shield. Easier to handle than a kite shield. The inverted hawk is the emblem of the company of slaves ordered to explore the Eternal City. </text>
<text> A medium-sized metal shield, comparatively easy to handle. Metal shields reliably negate physical damage when guarding, a trait which made them highly trusted on the battlefield. </text>
<text> Roundshield covered in black leather. On the larger side for a medium-sized shield. From the north, this shield depicts the polar star in rivets of gold. The inside is lined with fur, protecting the carrier from frost. </text>
<text> Tower shield engraved with a dragon, symbol of protection. Heavy even among greatshields, it possesses exceptional guarding ability. The ancient dragons, who ruled in the prehistoric era before the Erdtree, would protect their lord as a wall of living rock. </text>
<text> Greatshield featuring sumptuous ornamentation used by the scions of great families. Due to their excessive size, these shields were at times seen as the hallmark of little lordlings who were too timid to earn a few nicks and scratches. </text>
<text> Greatshield of red-tinged gold carried by Crucible Knights. Features a great horn. An ancient holiness dwells within. The crucible horn skewers foes when performing shield bashes. </text>
<text> Greatshield said to have been whittled from the claw of a great, ancient dragon, wielded by grotesque Tree Sentinels who yet serve the Erdtree. Imbued with lightning. </text>
<text> Greatshield from a foreign land, used by Elemer of the Briar. Attacks with this armament utilize the iron thorns that have been wound around its frame. Originates from Eochaid, a land of proudly solitary ascetics. </text>
<text> Weighty greatshield forged of gold carried by the order of Tree Sentinels, heavily equipped knights. Blessed by an old incantation of protection. The living rampart of the Erdtree, the Tree Sentinels are the standard to which all defenders of the Erdtree aspire. </text>
<text> Shield of dull gold with a beast engraved as its crest. Lighter than most greatshields, and subsequently easier to wield. The beast depicted is Serosh, aged counselor who guides the golden lineage. </text>
<text> The head of a spirit jellyfish, commonly found floating above sacred ground throughout the Lands Between, wielded without modification as a shield. The see-through head is extremely light, but its flesh is supple, providing absolutely no protection from piercing attacks. </text>
<text> A great stone shield with an intricately carved fingerprint design. One of the heaviest of all greatshields. Part of the tomb of an ancient god, the Readerless Fingers relayed their message through these imprints, said to be the very seeds from which frenzy first sprouted. </text>
<text> Greatshield painted with a divine scene; the recipience of a blessed tear from the Erdtree. An item that looks back fondly on the age of plenty. The divine scene acts in and of itself as a sacred invocation; gradually restoring the carrier's HP. </text>
<text> Tricksome shield made from white stone depicting a malformed one-eyed god. The barrel of a firearm pokes through the open mouth. Once worshipped by the giants, this evil deity is believed to have been slain by Queen Marika. </text>
<text> Tricksome bronze shield depicting the face of a Fire Giant. Several tongues leap from its open mouth. The dreadful visage and burning flames are designed to remind one of the horror of facing a Fire Giant. In other words, this shield has an instructional function. </text>
<text> A large wooden shield covered with spikes. Though relatively light, it lacks in damage negation. Designed to perform shield bashes, these attacks riddle the enemy with holes, earning it the nickname of "pard shield." </text>
<text> An iron greatshield large enough to cover the entire body. Depicts the Roundtable Hold, gathering place of champions. Greatshields boast high damage negation and guard capacity, making enemy attacks easy to repel. </text>
<text> An iron greatshield large enough to cover the entire body. Emblazoned with an old, interleaving tree. Greatshields boast high damage negation and guard capacity, making enemy attacks easy to repel. </text>
<text> An iron greatshield large enough to cover the entire body. Features an inverted hawk crest. Greatshields boast high damage negation and guard capacity, making enemy attacks easy to repel. </text>
<text> Huge head of one of the giant ants which inhabit the two underground rivers, used without modification as a shield. Excels at repelling enemy attacks. Giant ants are venomous creatures, granting a boost to immunity when wielding this shield. </text>
<text> Greatshield shaped like a fang, featuring the crest of red-maned lion. Carried by the Redmane Knights who fought alongside Radahn. </text>
<text> Metal greatshield painted with a sun in eclipse. Carried by the headless mausoleum knights. The eclipsed sun, drained of color, is the protective star of soulless demigods. It aids the mausoleum knights by keeping Destined Death at bay. </text>
<text> Metal greatshield painted with a peering cuckoo. Carried by the enchanted knights sworn to the academy. Boasting high magic damage negation, this shield is used to hunt down mages. "Our enemy is none other than Caria itself." </text>
<text> Oval greatshield made of gold, carried by knights who protect the Royal Capital of Leyndell. Knights of Leyndell are reputed for their sturdiness, exemplified by this shield's exceptional guard capacity. </text>
<text> Metal greatshield coated with gold. Carried by knights loyal to Godrick. The red tinge in the gold coat mirrors the primordial matter that became the Erdtree. The color of homeward yearning. </text>
<text> Metal greatshield depicting the Haligtree with unalloyed gold. Carried by knights who have vowed to serve Miquella's Haligtree. Possesses high holy damage negation. Yet now, with the Haligtree misshapen, this wondrous rendition is a fleeting fantasy. </text>
<text> Wooden greatshield reinforced with a metal ornamentation. Greatshields boast high damage negation and guard capacity, making enemy attacks easy to repel. </text>
<text> Wooden tower shield. Lightweight for a greatshield and easy to handle. Commonly used in the Shattering. Greatshields boast high damage negation and guard capacity, making enemy attacks easy to repel. </text>
<text> Staff with a glintstone embedded at the tip. A catalyst for casting sorceries. Sorceries must be memorized first at a site of lost grace, and a staff must be equipped to cast them. </text>
<text> Staff fashioned from pure crystal; a deed impossible for a human. Enhances Crystalian sorceries. The Crystalian's faint cogitation is known as the "wisdom of stone." This staff can only be wielded by those of intellect high enough to grasp such wisdom. </text>
<text> Staff with a forked tip, embedded with red glintstones. Enhances lava sorceries. The Man-Serpents of Mt. Gelmir draw from faith in addition to intelligence to enhance the potency of their sorcery. </text>
<text> Glintstone staff styled as a scepter. A gift once given to the demi-humans to foster peace, it can be wielded even by those of low intelligence. Sneered at by fools in the academy. </text>
<text> Magic scepter of Rennala, Queen of the Full Moon. The glintstone is known as a Carian Blue, enhancing full moon sorceries. Only those of the highest intelligence may wield this, the finest of all glintstone staves. </text>
<text> Staff of a sorcerer-miner who extracts glintstone from crystal tunnels. The staff itself is a tool used to mine, and the ferrule is also embedded with a glintstone. Boosts the power of Stonedigger sorceries. </text>
<text> Staff of the astrologers. A glintstone is embedded in the tip, enabling it to be used a catalyst for sorceries. Sorceries must be memorized first at a site of lost grace, and a staff must be equipped to cast them. </text>
<text> Staff embedded with a blue glintstone. One of two types of Carian staff. Gifted to enchanted knights, it enhances Glintblade sorceries. </text>
<text> Staff embedded with sullied amber, said to be a very part of the Prince of Death. Enhances death sorceries. One of the staves deemed heretical by the academy for its ability to allow sorceries to be augmented through faith in addition to intelligence. </text>
<text> Short staff with a blue glintstone embedded. Wielded by the Albinaurics of old. The Albinaurics harbor a secret; they cast sorcery using their innate arcaneness. </text>
<text> Staff of the Academy of Raya Lucaria, embedded with a turquoise glintstone. Only a recognized sorcerer is permitted to wield this staff. </text>
<text> Staff embedded with a blue glintstone. One of two types of Carian staff. Given to sorcerers that they might enact the role of knight. Enhances Carian sword sorceries. </text>
<text> Staff of the primeval glintstone sorcerer Azur. Only those who have glimpsed what lies beyond the wisdom of stone may wield it. Reduces casting time of all sorceries, but consumes additional FP. </text>
<text> Staff of the primeval glintstone sorcerer Lusat. Only those who have glimpsed what lies beyond the wisdom of stone may wield it. Enhances power of all sorceries, but consumes additional FP. </text>
<text> Staff embedded with a dark purple glintstone, said to be the fragment of a meteorite. Boasts high sorcery scaling and boosts gravity sorceries as well. However, this staff cannot be strengthened in any way. </text>
<text> A heretical staff fashioned from a smoldering, withered sapling that turns the blood of sacrifices pierced by it into glintstone. Similar to hex magic. Sorceries are scaled with faith rather than intelligence when wielding this staff which enhances thorn sorceries in particular. </text>
<text> Staff fashioned from pure crystal; a deed impossible for a human. It festers with scarlet rot. Enhances Crystalian sorceries. </text>
<text> Staff missing its glintstone. Wielded by sorcerers who believe that discovery comes through acts of asceticism. This staff is only capable of casting invisibility sorceries, but that is reason enough for some to wield it. </text>
<text> A sacred seal bestowed by Finger Maiden which serves as a catalyst for casting sacred incantations. Incantations must be memorized first at a site of grace, and a sacred seal must be equipped to cast them. </text>
<text> Sacred seal of the Godskin Apostles, inlaid with obsidian. Said to represent the manipulation of black flame, this catalyst enhances godslayer incantations. </text>
<text> Sacred seal depicting the one-eyed god of the Fire Giants, adorned with braids of red hair. Sacred seal wielded by Fire Monks and Prelates, this catalyst enhances Giants' Flame incantations. </text>
<text> Sacred seal made from Gravel Stone thought to be an ancient dragon scale. Enhances Dragon Cult incantations of the Royal Capital. The worship of the ancient dragons does not conflict with belief in the Erdtree. After all, this seal, and lighting itself, are both imbued with gold. </text>
<text> Sacred seal granted by Gurranq, the Beast Clergyman. A rare trinket which allows incantations to be scaled with strength. The claw mark represents Gurranq's wrath. Enhances bestial incantations learned from Gurranq. </text>
<text> A formless sacred seal depicting the ceremonial observation of Order. Enhances Golden Order Fundamentalist incantations. Fundamentalism is scholarship in all but name. Scales incantations using both intelligence and faith. </text>
<text> A formless sacred seal decorated with an Erdtree crest, once the focus of religion in the Lands Between. Even though the Elden Ring is shattered, and the Erdtree has dulled from its former radiance, earnest faith continues to hold the answers. </text>
<text> Formless drakeblood seal with a dragon communion crest. Enhances Dragon Communion incantations. The sacrificial devouring of the heart gives power. Indeed, Dragon Communion is too primal in nature for the term "incantation" to be appropriate. This seal scales incantations with one's arcane attribute. </text>
<text> Formless sacred seal bestowed by the maiden of the Three Fingers. Enhances incantations of the frenzied flame. This seal is the mark of the Lord of Frenzied Flame. Scales incantations using strength, dexterity, intelligence, and faith all together. </text>
<text> Small bow made to fire arrows over great distances. Other than its ability to fire off arrows in rapid succession, it is also well-suited for use on horseback. To use a bow, arrows must also be equipped. </text>
<text> Shortbow wielded by Winged Misbegotten. Fine fur clings to it. Designed to inflict additional damage by sacrificing range. </text>
<text> Shortbow of polished red wood. Fashioned by a master craftsman and wielded by pages. A bow which requires dexterity rather than strength to master. </text>
<text> Bow fashioned from a minstrel's harp. Sonorous tones still resound when firing arrows. Troubadours sing tales of champions, both in the honorable service of the Erdtree, and the one who spurns honor for blasphemy. </text>
<text> Bow composited from a mix of materials. Demands high attributes, and is tricky to wield, but is a fearsome tool when mastered. </text>
<text> Longbow made to fire arrows over great distances. Compared to a shortbow, arrows fired reach further and deal more damage. To use a bow, arrows must also be equipped. </text>
<text> Longbow featuring delicate silverwork. Wielded by Albinauric wolfback archers. This bow requires dexterity over strength to master. </text>
<text> Longbow made from animal horn. Wielded by the master hunters of the ancestral followers. Imbues arrows fired with magic damage. Reveals its true worth when used with magic-infused arrows. </text>
<text> Longbow featuring Erdtree styling. In times of old, when faith and battle went hand in hand, this weapon was created in tandem with the Golden Arrow. Scales all arrow damage with faith, revealing its true worth when used with holy-infused arrows. </text>
<text> Malformed bow in the shape of a pair of poisonous snakes. Imbues arrows with poison through pagan magic, revealing its true worth when used with poison-infused arrows. Used by assassins known as the Formless Serpents. </text>
<text> Longbow which utilizes a series of pulleys and springs. The complex mechanism, which required advanced mathematical and mechanical understanding to craft, was likely made by a certain genius who learned Golden Order fundamentalism. Enhances precision while shooting, enabling arrows to fly much further distances. </text>
<text> Longbow carved from black wood to resemble a blade. One of the most difficult bows to master. The blade-like body of the bow is light and cuts through the air. Though a longbow, it can be wielded similarly to a shortbow. </text>
<text> Greatbow of black iron wielded by General Radahn. Decorated with a lion mane motif. Imbued with gravitational power of the Starscourge, when used along with Radahn's Spear, it becomes a true weapon of a champion. </text>
<text> Greatbow of black stone crafted by a civilization now gone to ruin. Weapon of the Guardian Golem. Extremely heavy, this greatbow requires enormous strength just to draw, suggesting it was not designed for human use. </text>
<text> Greatbow featuring Erdtree styling. In times of old, when faith and battle went hand in hand, this weapon was created in tandem with the Golden Great Arrow. Scales all arrow damage with faith, revealing its true worth when used with holy-infused arrows. </text>
<text> Enormous greatbow larger than any man. Can not be drawn with any ordinary level of strength, but the force of its shots is extraordinary. A greatbow can only fire great arrows. </text>
<text> A crossbow of simple make, usable by anyone, but lacking in both power and accuracy. Bolts must be equipped to use a crossbow. </text>
<text> Ranged weapon made from a bow fixed to a stock. Deals good damage and is simple to use, but requires reloading after firing. Bolts must be equipped to use a crossbow. </text>
<text> Heavy crossbow with iron limbs, increasing damage dealt. Commonly employed in the Shattering. </text>
<text> Crossbow made with pulleys and power springs. The complex mechanism, which required advanced mathematical and mechanical understanding to craft, was likely made by a certain genius who learned Golden Order fundamentalism. One touch fires a volley of bolts. Be warned; large stores of bolts can be quickly spent. </text>
<text> One-of-a-kind enchanted crossbow of exquisitely detailed craftsmanship. Made to celebrate the matrimonial union, and reconciliation, between the houses of the Erdtree and the Full Moon, Leyndell and Raya Lucaria. The two rings dance when reloading the weapon. Reveals true worth when used with holy-infused bolts. </text>
<text> Large crossbow made from composite materials. One of the largest of all bolt-firing devices. Its limbs are more pliable than metallic ones, allowing bolts fired from this weapon to pierce even helms forged of steel. </text>
<text> Black crossbow featuring a long stock. Used for sniping, it has a very long range. Weapon of Crepus, who served the Two Fingers from the shadows of the Roundtable as the head confessor. </text>
<text> An unconventional ballistic device modelled on a weapon used to besiege castles. Only capable of firing greatbolts. Perfect for reckless acts such as storming a castle or facing an entire army alone. </text>
<text> Jar cannon which uses explosives to fire greatbolts. Deals great damage but is slow to reload. Experimental firearm brought to the assault on Volcano Manor, where it was discovered that no one knew how to use it. </text>
<text> Arrows used with small and long bows. Unremarkable in any way, shape or form. </text>
<text> Arrow with the tip set alight. Deals fire damage. </text>
<text> Arrow carved to resemble a flying snake. Used in tandem with the Serpent Bow. Loyal minions of the Formless Serpents, their fangs are daubed with deadly poison. </text>
<text> Arrow whittled from thin animal bones. Craftable item. The feather fletching adds distance to the arrow's flight. </text>
<text> Arrow carved to resemble a withered water lily. Afflicts targets with a powerful sleep effect. Priests of St. Trina use these arrows to spread their teachings. The sweet oblivion of sleep can become quite the habit. </text>
<text> Arrow whittled from animal bones tipped with a shard of crystal. Creates a resonating noise at the point of impact. Craftable item. The fletching adds distance to the arrow's flight. </text>
<text> Arrow whittled from animal bones tipped with chips of Rainbow Stone. Colored light shines at the point of impact. Craftable item. The fletching adds distance to the arrow's flight. </text>
<text> Carved arrows made in tandem with the Erdtree Bow. Deals holy damage. Highly effective against Those Who Live in Death, and able to prevent them from rising again. </text>
<text> Arrow in which the spirits of small animals are thought to dwell. Deals magic damage. Used by the master hunters of the ancestral followers. </text>
<text> Arrow whittled from thin animal bones. Craftable item. Though the tip is certainly sharp, it does not fly particularly true. </text>
<text> Arrow whittled from animal bones. The tip is set alight before firing. Deals fire damage. Craftable item. The fletching adds distance to the arrow's flight. </text>
<text> Arrow whittled from animal bones. The tip is set alight before firing. Deals fire damage. Craftable item. </text>
<text> Arrow whittled from animal bones. The tip is daubed with venom. Afflicts targets with poison. Craftable item. The fletching adds distance to the arrow's flight. </text>
<text> Arrow whittled from animal bones. The tip is daubed with venom. Afflicts targets with poison. Craftable item. </text>
<text> Arrow whittled from animal bones. The tip is daubed with a water lily tincture. Afflicts targets with sleep. Craftable item. The fletching adds distance to the arrow's flight. </text>
<text> Arrow whittled from animal bones. The tip is daubed with a water lily tincture. Afflicts targets with sleep. Craftable item. </text>
<text> Arrow whittled from animal bones fletched with stormhawk feathers. Craftable item. Flies enshrouded in storm winds, breaking enemy stances and guards with ease. </text>
<text> Arrow whittled from animal bones with a lightning-infused tip. Deals lightning damage. Craftable item. The fletching adds distance to the arrow's flight. </text>
<text> Arrow whittled from animal bones with a lightning-infused tip. Deals lightning damage. Craftable item. </text>
<text> Arrow whittled from animal bones tipped with chips of Rainbow Stone. Colored light shines at the point of impact. Craftable item. </text>
<text> Arrow whittled from animal bones tipped with a shard of crystal. Creates a resonating noise at the point of impact. Craftable item. </text>
<text> Arrow set alight with ghostflame before firing. Deals magic damage while also afflicting foes with frost. Used by the Company of the Fallen Hawk, once ordered to explore the Eternal City. </text>
<text> Arrow whittled from animal bones. The tip is daubed with a glintstone tincture. Deals magic damage. Craftable item. The fletching adds distance to the arrow's flight. </text>
<text> Arrow whittled from animal bones. The tip is daubed with a glintstone tincture. Deals magic damage. Craftable item. </text>
<text> Arrow whittled from animal bones. The tip is daubed with a golden tincture. Deals holy damage. Craftable item. The fletching adds distance to the arrow's flight. </text>
<text> Arrow whittled from animal bones. The tip is daubed with a golden tincture. Deals holy damage. Craftable item. </text>
<text> Arrow whittled from animal bones. The tip is daubed with a blood tincture. Afflicts targets with blood loss. Craftable item. The fletching adds distance to the arrow's flight. </text>
<text> Arrow whittled from animal bones. The tip is daubed with a blood tincture. Afflicts targets with blood loss. Craftable item. </text>
<text> Arrow whittled from animal bones with a frozen tip. Afflicts targets with frost. Craftable item. The fletching adds distance to the arrow's flight. </text>
<text> Arrow whittled from animal bones with a frozen tip. Afflicts targets with frost. Craftable item. </text>
<text> Arrow whittled from animal bones. The tip is daubed with rot. Afflicts targets with scarlet rot. Craftable item. The fletching adds distance to the arrow's flight. </text>
<text> Arrow whittled from animal bones. The tip is daubed with rot. Afflicts targets with scarlet rot. Craftable item. </text>
<text> A greatarrow as large as a spear for use with greatbows. Used by archers of monstrous strength employed by a lord's army. </text>
<text> Greatarrow of black stone crafted by a civilization now gone to ruin. Used by the Guardian Golem. This hefty arrow is enrobed in tempestuous winds, allowing it to break enemy stances and guards with ease. </text>
<text> Carved greatarrows made together with the Erdtree Greatbow. Deals holy damage. Imbued with an oath-sworn incantation, which boosts the attack and defense of the archer and their nearby allies. </text>
<text> Greatarrow of black stone crafted by a civilization now gone to ruin. Imbued with its ancient magic. Deals magic damage. </text>
<text> Greatarrows used by General Radahn during the festival of combat. These are in fact the many spears with which he was stabbed by the Cleanrot Knights. Imbued with Radahn's gravitational power. </text>
<text> Greatarrow as large as a spear whittled from stout animal bones. Craftable item. The fletching adds distance to the arrow's flight. </text>
<text> Greatarrow as large as a spear whittled from stout animal bones. Though the tip is certainly sharp, it does not fly particularly true. </text>
<text> Ammunition used for crossbows. A widespread, common type of bolt. </text>
<text> Bolt tipped with a shard of Gravel Stone. Deals powerful lightning damage. Used by worshippers of the ancient dragons. </text>
<text> Bolt created with perfumer techniques. Used by nobles' guards and the like. The point of impact explodes with sparks, dealing fire damage. </text>
<text> Bolts used in Crepus' Black-Key Crossbow, an assassin's tool of exquisite craftsmanship. The intricate spiral tip bores deep, injecting scarlet rot far into the flesh of its target. </text>
<text> Bolt covered in thorns. One of the most horrific weapons used in the Shattering. Afflicts target with blood loss. Difficult to remove once buried in flesh, causing appalling damage to the body. </text>
<text> Enchanted work of craft made in tandem with the Full Moon Crossbow. The tip is embedded with glintstone. Like a shooting star, these bolts leave a beautiful trail when fired. Deals magic damage. </text>
<text> Bolt tipped with a shard of Explosive Stone. Explodes on impact, dealing fire damage. </text>
<text> Bolt blessed with an incantation of the Erdtree. Deals powerful holy damage. Once used by guards of the Capital. </text>
<text> Well-crafted bolt with an illustrious design, wielded by regulars of a lord's army. Deals more damage than its commonplace cousin. </text>
<text> Bolt carved from a thin animal bone. Craftable item. Though the tip is certainly sharp, it does not fly particularly true. </text>
<text> Bolt carved from animal bone. The tip is set alight before firing. Deals fire damage. Craftable item. </text>
<text> Bolt crafted from animal bone with a lightning-infused tip. Deals lightning damage. Craftable item. </text>
<text> Bolt carved from animal bone. The tip is daubed with a glintstone tincture. Deals magic damage. Craftable item. </text>
<text> Bolt carved from animal bone. The tip is daubed with a golden tincture. Deals holy damage. Craftable item. </text>
<text> Bolt carved from animal bone. The tip is daubed with venom. Afflicts targets with poison. Craftable item. </text>
<text> Bolt carved from animal bone. The tip is daubed with a blood tincture. Afflicts targets with blood loss. Craftable item. </text>
<text> Bolt carved from animal bone with a frozen tip. Afflicts targets with frost. Craftable item. </text>
<text> Bolt carved from animal bone. The tip is daubed with rot. Afflicts targets with scarlet rot. Craftable item. </text>
<text> Bolt carved from animal bone. The tip is daubed with a waterlily tincture. Afflicts targets with sleep. Craftable item. </text>
<text> Bolt with a fiercely burned tip. Deals powerful fire damage. Used by survivors of Radahn's army to stave off the scarlet rot. </text>
<text> Greatbolt as large as a spear for use with Hand Ballista. </text>
<text> Greatbolt tipped with a clump of Gravel Stone shards. Deals powerful lightning damage. </text>
<text> Greatbolt tipped with a clump of Explosive Stone shards. Detonates a large explosion on impact, dealing fire damage. </text>

</entries>